<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 11:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Directing the United States Flag to be Flown at Half-Staff in Memory of Charlie Kirk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation issued by the President states that the flag of the United States shall be flown at half-staff as a mark of respect for the memory of Charlie Kirk. The proclamation is issued under the authority vested in the President by the Constitution and the laws of the United States. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/honoring-the-memory-of-charlie-kirk/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/honoring-the-memory-of-charlie-kirk/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of the United States–Japan Agreement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President, exercising authority under the Constitution and statutes including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, announces actions to implement the United States–Japan Agreement. The document cites these authorities and describes the measures taken to execute the bilateral agreement, outlining the framework for implementation and the statutory basis for the executive action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/implementing-the-united-states-japan-agreement/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/implementing-the-united-states-japan-agreement/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Tammy Bruce to be Deputy United States Representative to the United Nations with ambassadorial rank]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Tammy Bruce of California has been nominated to serve as the Deputy United States Representative to the United Nations, with the rank and status of Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary, and as the Deputy United States Representative to the United Nations Security Council. The nomination also provides for concurrent service in an additional capacity without additional compensation, as described in the White House notices accompanying nominations sent to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>