<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for U.S. Director of the African Development Bank and Federal Labor Relations Authority General Counsel]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for three positions: Ademola Adewale-Sadik to be United States Director of the African Development Bank for a five-year term, succeeding Oren E. Whyche-Shaw; Charlton Allen to be General Counsel of the Federal Labor Relations Authority for a five-year term, succeeding Julia Akins Clark; and Matthew Anderson, for another position, with further details not provided in the excerpt. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-078c/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-078c/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Directive to Withdraw the United States from International Organizations, Conventions, and Treaties Contrary to United States Interests]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President directs the heads of executive departments and agencies to implement withdrawal from international organizations, conventions, and treaties that have been determined to be contrary to United States interests. The directive instructs agencies to terminate U.S. participation, cease funding commitments associated with the identified entities, and harmonize ongoing activities with the withdrawal. It requires identifying and addressing obligations arising from participation, notifying relevant international bodies as required, and completing withdrawal actions within established timelines. The directive assigns responsibilities across federal agencies to ensure orderly disengagement consistent with applicable law. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order: Prioritizing Warfighter Needs in Defense Contracting]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action directs federal agencies to prioritize the needs and readiness of the U.S. armed forces in defense contracting, guiding procurement decisions to better align contracts with operational requirements, and establishing oversight measures to improve efficiency, accountability, and alignment of defense contracts with stated military objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for U.S. Attorney for the District of Maine and U.S. District Judge for the Western District of Missouri, Among Other Nominations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House reports nominations sent to the Senate, including Andrew Benson to be United States Attorney for the District of Maine for a four-year term (succeeding Darcie N. McElwee) and Megan Blair Benton to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri (succeeding the retiring M. Douglas Harpool). The post notes additional nominations, including William Boyle of North Carolina for another United States position, among others. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Amending Adjustments to Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation, issued by the President of the United States, implements amendments to regulations governing the importation of timber, lumber, and their derivative products into the United States under Section 232. It references the Secretary of Commerce's report dated July 1, 2025, on the effects of these imports on national security and states that the amendments adjust the existing measures governing such imports based on the findings of that report. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>