<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:00:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Withdrawing the United States from International Organizations, Conventions, and Treaties Contrary to U.S. Interests]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum directs the heads of executive departments and agencies to implement withdrawal from international organizations, conventions, and treaties deemed contrary to the interests of the United States, building on Executive Order 14199 issued February 4, 2025, and to end funding to those entities. It outlines the objective, scope, and procedural steps for identifying eligible organizations and treaties, coordinating withdrawal actions across agencies, and terminating related funding, with specified agency responsibilities and reporting requirements. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Prioritize Warfighter Requirements in Defense Contracting]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued by the President, directs federal agencies to place the needs of U.S. military personnel at the forefront of defense contracting decisions. It reiterates the President's commitment to ensuring that the United States military maintains highly capable and lethal warfighting capabilities and directs agency actions to align procurement policies and contractor performance with warfighter requirements, with the aim of strengthening national defense. The order emphasizes prioritizing defense programs and contracting outcomes that directly support combat readiness and battlefield effectiveness. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate: Andrew Benson for U.S. Attorney, District of Maine; Megan Blair Benton for U.S. District Judge, Western District of Missouri; William Boyle for United States position]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate, including Andrew Benson, of Maine, to be United States Attorney for the District of Maine for a four-year term (succeeding Darcie N. McElwee); Megan Blair Benton, of Missouri, to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri (succeeding M. Douglas Harpool, who is retiring); and William Boyle, of North Carolina, to be United States [position unspecified in excerpt]. The notice appears on the White House website under Nominations Sent to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation on Amendments to Adjusting Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Proclamation states that, on July 1, 2025, the Secretary of Commerce transmitted to the President a report regarding the effects of imports of timber, lumber, and their derivative products on the national security of the United States under section 232. It announces amendments to the regulatory framework for adjusting imports of these wood products into the United States, in response to the findings or considerations associated with that section 232 investigation. The document describes the actions taken to implement changes to how such imports are adjusted and references the ongoing national security review related to these products. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action to Implement the United States-Israel Agreement on Trade in Agricultural Products and for Other Purposes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action implements the United States-Israel Agreement on Trade in Agricultural Products as part of the United States-Israel Free Trade Area (USIFTA). It references Congress's approval of the framework under the United States–Israel Free Trade Area Implementation Act and directs the relevant federal agencies to take the necessary steps to carry out the Agreement's trade provisions and related purposes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/to-implement-the-united-states-israel-agreement-on-trade-in-agricultural-products-and-for-other-purposes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/to-implement-the-united-states-israel-agreement-on-trade-in-agricultural-products-and-for-other-purposes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Adjustments of Certain Rates of Pay for Statutory Pay Systems]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order exercises presidential authority to set and adjust the rates of basic pay for federal employees covered by statutory pay systems, as defined in 5 U.S.C. 5302(1). The adjustments are made under 5 U.S.C. 5303, and apply to the basic pay or salaries of those systems as specified in the order. The order begins with Section 1, addressing Statutory Pay Systems, and establishes the revised pay rates for applicable employees in accordance with the statutory framework. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Advancing American Space Capabilities and National Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive order issued by the President under constitutional and legal authority to establish the objectives for maintaining and advancing United States space capabilities. The order defines space superiority as a strategic aim and describes how domestically developed technologies contribute to the nation's strength, security, and prosperity. Section 1 outlines the purpose, framing space superiority as an indicator of national vision and will, and motivating the actions to enhance the United States' space capabilities for national security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>