<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying the Scope of the Reciprocal Tariff for Certain Agricultural Products]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President, invoking authorities under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, announces a modification to the scope of the reciprocal tariff as it applies to certain agricultural products. The action identifies the legal basis for the modification and describes how the tariff treatment for the specified agricultural products will be adjusted within the reciprocal tariff framework. The modification is part of the administration's ongoing tariff policy under these statutes, and it specifies the affected products and any relevant implementation details as set forth in the order. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President of the United States on Veterans Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation honors the courage, honor, and service of U.S. veterans, acknowledges their sacrifices in defending freedom and the nation’s way of life, and designates Veterans Day, 2025, with appropriate observances reflecting on nearly 250 years of veterans’ contributions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Marine Corps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation commemorates the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Marine Corps. It describes the establishment and the corps' continued role in national defense, and it calls for appropriate observances to recognize the Marine Corps' history and service. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jared Isaacman to be Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jared Isaacman, a resident of Pennsylvania, has been nominated to serve as Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration. The nomination is intended to succeed Bill Nelson, who has resigned. The nomination has been sent to the Senate for consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying Reciprocal Tariff Rates Under the U.S.–China Economic and Trade Arrangement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action modifies the reciprocal tariff rates applicable to goods covered by the bilateral economic and trade arrangement between the United States and the People's Republic of China. The modification is issued by the President under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, as amended. The action sets forth the adjusted tariff rates, the scope of goods affected by the arrangement, and the implementation details described in the accompanying documentation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying Tariff Duties to Address the Synthetic Opioid Supply Chain in the People’s Republic of China]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President invokes authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974 to modify tariff duties on imports from the People’s Republic of China. The action is intended to address concerns related to the synthetic opioid supply chain. The directive directs relevant federal agencies to implement the revised duties and to enforce them in accordance with applicable law. The action is published on The White House website as part of presidential actions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>