<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President Declaring Patriot Day 2025, the 24th Anniversary of the September 11 Terrorist Attacks]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation designates September 11, 2025, as Patriot Day to honor the victims of the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks and to acknowledge the service and sacrifice of first responders and others who contributed to the nation’s recovery. It calls for national observances and participation in appropriate commemorative activities across federal, state, and local communities, including a moment of remembrance at 8:46 a.m. local time and the display of the flag in accordance with customary observances. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum to the Secretary of Health and Human Services and the Commissioner of Food and Drugs on Direct-to-Consumer Prescription Drug Advertising]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum addresses direct-to-consumer prescription drug advertising and the role of the Food and Drug Administration. It notes that FDA authority to regulate prescription drug advertising has been established since 1962 and discusses concerns about the potential for misleading presentation of risks and benefits, emphasis on medications over lifestyle changes, possible influence on the physician-patient relationship, and the use of higher-cost drugs. The document outlines objective considerations for improving accuracy, balance, and transparency in direct-to-consumer advertising and may propose policy options or actions for strengthening regulatory practices by the Department of Health and Human Services and the FDA. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-for-the-secretary-of-health-and-human-services-the-commissioner-of-food-and-drugs/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-for-the-secretary-of-health-and-human-services-the-commissioner-of-food-and-drugs/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Restoring the United States Department of War]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs the restoration of the United States Department of War and describes its intended purposes and scope within the executive branch. It references the department’s original establishment on August 7, 1789 by President George Washington and Congress to oversee its operation and maintenance, and outlines the reestablishment of the department and its role within the federal government’s defense-related functions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-the-united-states-department-of-war/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-the-united-states-department-of-war/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Modifying the Scope of Reciprocal Tariffs and Establishing Procedures for Implementing Trade and Security Agreements]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action modifies the scope of reciprocal tariffs and establishes procedures for implementing trade and security agreements. It is authorized by the Constitution and the laws of the United States, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/modifying-the-scope-of-reciprocal-tariffs-and-establishing-procedures-for-implementing-trade-and-security-agreements/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/modifying-the-scope-of-reciprocal-tariffs-and-establishing-procedures-for-implementing-trade-and-security-agreements/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Strengthen Protections for U.S. Nationals from Wrongful Detention Abroad]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Issued under the authority of the Constitution and the Levinson Hostage Recovery and Hostage-Taking Accountability Act, this executive order states the federal government's objective to strengthen efforts to protect U.S. nationals from wrongful detention abroad. It directs federal agencies to coordinate actions to prevent such detentions, to respond effectively when they occur, and to enhance accountability mechanisms related to wrongful detention. The order emphasizes interagency cooperation, information sharing, and monitoring to safeguard the rights and safety of U.S. nationals overseas. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/strengthening-efforts-to-protect-u-s-nationals-from-wrongful-detention-abroad/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/strengthening-efforts-to-protect-u-s-nationals-from-wrongful-detention-abroad/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate: Erwin Antoni for Commissioner of Labor Statistics; Laura DiBella for Federal Maritime Commissioner; Steven Haines for Assistant Secretary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for three individuals: Erwin Antoni, of Pennsylvania, to be Commissioner of Labor Statistics for a four-year term, to succeed Erika L. McEntarfer; Laura DiBella, of Florida, to be Federal Maritime Commissioner for a term expiring June 30, 2028, to succeed L. E. Sola; and Steven Haines, of Virginia, to be an Assistant Secretary (department not specified in the excerpt). The announcements were published on the White House website as part of nominations sent to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-f7c7/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-f7c7/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Restoring and Enhancing Federal Civic Architecture]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes the policy to restore and improve the design quality of federal civic architecture. It references the Founders' view that federal public buildings should inspire the public and support civic life. The order directs federal agencies to prioritize architectural quality in the planning, design, and construction of new federal facilities, to align projects with historical and civic design traditions where appropriate, and to enhance the overall appearance and accessibility of federal properties. It also calls for coordination with design authorities and mechanisms to monitor progress toward beautification and modernization goals. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/making-federal-architecture-beautiful-again/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/making-federal-architecture-beautiful-again/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>