<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Adjust the Rates of Basic Pay for Federal Statutory Pay Systems]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs adjustments to the rates of basic pay or salaries for the United States federal statutory pay systems, as defined in 5 U.S.C. 5302(1), with adjustments made under 5 U.S.C. 5303. The document establishes the applicable statutory framework for determining pay levels and sets the updated pay rates for employees covered by these statutory pay systems. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Establish and Maintain United States Space Superiority]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order sets forth the policy and actions for pursuing and sustaining United States space superiority. It states that leadership in space reflects national goals and capabilities, and that the development of space-related technologies contributes to the nation’s strength, security, and prosperity. The order calls for coordinated efforts across relevant federal agencies to advance space capabilities, ensure resilience of space infrastructure, address potential threats to space assets, and support national security and economic interests, with an emphasis on maintaining and enhancing U.S. space capabilities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Declaring Federal Government Office Closures on December 24, 2025, and December 26, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive order, issued under the President's constitutional and statutory authority, directs that all executive departments and agencies of the Federal Government be closed and their employees be excused from duty on Wednesday, December 24, 2025, and Friday, December 26, 2025, establishing a government-wide temporary closure for those dates. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action to Increase Medical Marijuana and Cannabidiol Research]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action states the administration's policy to expand research into medical marijuana and cannabidiol and to improve access to advanced medical treatments and research infrastructure. It references the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's 2023 review as part of the justification for expanding research and outlines the initial section on the purpose and policy of the action, detailing the objective to enhance federal support for evaluating medical uses of marijuana and cannabidiol. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/increasing-medical-marijuana-and-cannabidiol-research/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/increasing-medical-marijuana-and-cannabidiol-research/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Restricting and Limiting the Entry of Foreign Nationals to Protect the Security of the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs restrictions and limitations on entry for certain foreign nationals into the United States to address national security and public safety concerns at the border. It reinstates prior policies that were upheld by the Supreme Court and references Executive Order 14161, issued January 20, 2025, as the basis for these measures. The order outlines the scope of affected individuals, the entry criteria, and enforcement provisions intended to prevent admissions that could threaten United States security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/restricting-and-limiting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-security-of-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/restricting-and-limiting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-security-of-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>