<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President of the United States: National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On December 7, 2025, the President issues a proclamation designating National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day. The document honors the memory of those who died in the December 7, 1941 attack on Pearl Harbor and recognizes the enduring sacrifices of United States service members and civilians who contributed to the nation's defense. It invites all Americans to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies, moments of remembrance, and educational activities, and directs government offices and the public to observe this occasion with solemn reflection. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum to Align United States Core Childhood Vaccine Recommendations with International Best Practices]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential memorandum directed to the Secretary of Health and Human Services and the Director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention calls for aligning the United States core childhood vaccine recommendations with best practices observed in peer developed countries. It notes that in January 2025 the United States began recommending vaccination for all children against 18 diseases, including COVID-19, and tasks HHS and the CDC with evaluating current immunization guidelines and harmonizing them with international benchmarks and evidence-based practices seen in other high-income nations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates December 7, 2025 as National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day and invites the nation to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies and moments of remembrance, honoring the events of December 7, 1941 and recognizing the contributions and sacrifice of those who served. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate: James Bishop for U.S. Attorney (Middle District of North Carolina), Megan Blair Benton for U.S. District Judge (Western District of Missouri), and Christopher Michael De Bono for Associate Judge]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that nominations have been sent to the Senate for three federal positions: James Bishop, of North Carolina, to be United States Attorney for the Middle District of North Carolina for a four-year term; Megan Blair Benton, of Missouri, to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri; and Christopher Michael De Bono, of the District of Columbia, to be an Associate Judge of an unspecified court. The announcement indicates these nominations have been transmitted to the Senate for consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thanksgiving Day, 2025 Proclamation by the President of the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates Thanksgiving Day for 2025 on Thursday, November 27, and calls on the American people to observe the day with gratitude for the nation's blessings. It references the historical origins of Thanksgiving dating to the 18th century and describes the intended observances, including gatherings with family and community, reflection on national achievements, and acts of charity and service to others. The proclamation acknowledges the contributions of workers, farmers, and other members of society who support the country and encourages recognition of the day as a time for gratitude and unity across the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>