<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Religious Freedom Day, 2026 Proclamation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates Religious Freedom Day, 2026, and emphasizes the United States' longstanding commitment to the free exercise of religion. It notes that for 250 years the nation has upheld the principle that every person has the right to practice their faith, follow their conscience, and worship freely and without fear. The proclamation describes Religious Freedom Day as a nationwide observance to honor this fundamental right, recognize the contributions of religious communities, and reaffirm the duty of the government to protect liberty of conscience and worship for all Americans. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/religious-freedom-day-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/religious-freedom-day-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Semiconductors, Semiconductor Manufacturing Equipment, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation implements adjustments to the importation of semiconductors, semiconductor manufacturing equipment, and their derivative products into the United States. It references a report transmitted by the Secretary of Commerce on December 22, 2025 concerning the national security effects of these imports under section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962. Based on that report, the President directs modifications to the import regime for these items and identifies the scope of affected products. The proclamation outlines how the measures are to be implemented, the roles of the Secretary of Commerce and the President in enforcement, and any transitional arrangements or exemptions described within the document. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing a Second Emergency Board to Investigate Disputes Between the Long Island Rail Road Company and Certain of Its Employees Represented by Certain Labor Organizations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Presidential action establishing a second Emergency Board under the Railway Labor Act to investigate and report on disputes between the Long Island Rail Road Company and certain of its employees who are represented by the Transportation Communications Union, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. The Board is tasked with examining the issues in the disputes and to provide findings and recommendations to facilitate resolution and prevent service disruption. The establishment of this board is part of the process to address potential labor disputes in the railroad industry. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Modifying Imports of Processed Critical Minerals and Their Derivative Products into the United States under Section 232 National Security Investigation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issued a proclamation modifying the import regime for processed critical minerals and their derivative products (PCMDPs) into the United States. This action follows a national security investigation conducted under Section 232, after the Secretary of Commerce transmitted a report to the President on October 24, 2025 detailing the investigation's findings on the effects of PCMDPs on national security. The proclamation uses the authorities provided under Section 232 to implement adjustments to imports of PCMDPs and related derivative products to address identified national security concerns. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Safeguard Venezuelan Oil Revenue for the American and Venezuelan People]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An Executive Order issued under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act to safeguard revenue generated from Venezuela's oil sector. The order directs the implementation of policies and actions designed to prevent misappropriation, diversion, or illicit use of proceeds from Venezuelan oil. It authorizes the designation and blocking of individuals, properties, and transactions involved in illicit activity related to Venezuelan oil, and directs coordination among federal departments and agencies to identify, monitor, and enforce these measures. The objective is to ensure that Venezuelan oil revenue is used to support the Venezuelan people and align with U.S. policy objectives and security interests. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Regarding the Acquisition of Certain Assets of Emcore Corporation by Hiefo Corporation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This Executive Order, issued by the President under the Constitution and the Defense Production Act of 1950, as amended, including authority under Section 721 (50 U.S.C. 4565), establishes Section 1 Findings indicating there is credible evidence that leads the President to believe action is warranted concerning the acquisition of certain assets of Emcore Corporation by Hiefo Corporation. The order asserts the President's authority under the Defense Production Act to address the transaction and outlines the scope for government action consistent with the act, providing the basis for potential measures related to the specified asset acquisition under the applicable statute. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>