<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:00:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum Directing Enforcement of Federal Death Penalty Laws in the District of Columbia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential memorandum addressed to the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia directing consideration and enforcement of federal capital punishment statutes within the District of Columbia. The memorandum states that the authority is grounded in the Constitution and federal law and articulates the objective of deterring and punishing the most serious offenses by applying federal death penalty provisions where appropriate. It requests coordination among Federal prosecutors and, where applicable, District of Columbia authorities to determine eligibility for capital prosecution, manage capital case procedures, and ensure the provision of necessary resources while complying with applicable legal protections. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes-4a03/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes-4a03/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum 7: Countering Domestic Terrorism and Organized Political Violence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum 7, issued by the President, directs the Secretary of State, the Secretary of the Treasury, the Attorney General, and the Secretary of Homeland Security to coordinate and implement policy measures aimed at countering domestic terrorism and organized political violence within the United States. The memorandum establishes the authority of the President and outlines interagency roles and responsibilities, as well as the framework for policy development, coordination, and implementation to address domestic violent extremism and related activities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: Gold Star Mothers and Families Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates Gold Star Mothers and Families Day, 2025 as a national observance to honor the sacrifices of Gold Star Families (families of service members who died in the line of duty) and to recognize their contributions to the nation. The proclamation invites federal, state, and local governments, as well as the public, to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies and remembrance and to acknowledge the impact of this loss on families and the country. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Implementing the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act to Regulate Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications, Including TikTok]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to implement the provisions of Public Law 118-50, Division H, the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act, which regulates applications controlled by foreign adversaries. The order references TikTok as an example of such applications and establishes steps for assessing and mitigating national security risks associated with these applications, including authorization, oversight, and compliance actions by relevant departments and agencies. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Restricting Entry of Certain Nonimmigrant Workers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation restricting entry of certain nonimmigrant workers. The document notes that the H-1B visa program was created to admit temporary, high-skilled workers to the United States, but it asserts that the program has been exploited to replace American workers with lower-paid, lower-skilled labor rather than supplement the workforce. The proclamation establishes restrictions on entry for specific nonimmigrant categories and directs federal agencies to implement and enforce these measures to address concerns about job displacement and wage effects on American workers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating National POW/MIA Recognition Day for 2025, honoring service members who were prisoners of war or missing in action across historical conflicts, and urging observances and actions to commemorate their service, support their families, and continue efforts to account for missing personnel. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Gold Card: Executive Order on Immigration Policy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive action, issued under constitutional and statutory authority, establishes the purpose of reversing the immigration policies of the prior administration. The document notes that those prior policies led to a large influx of immigrants and indicates a need to reassess how immigrants are considered and processed under current policy, outlining the administration's objective to implement changes in immigration policy and administration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>