<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 11:00:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination Sent to the Senate for Louisiana District Judgeships and U.S. Marshal Appointment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President has nominated William J. Crain of Louisiana to be United States District Judge for the Eastern District of Louisiana to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Eldon E. Fallon, and Alexander C. Van Hook of Louisiana to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Louisiana to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Elizabeth Erny Foote. The President has also nominated Brian Barber of Louisiana to be United States Marshal for the state of Louisiana. The nominations have been transmitted to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Energy Dominance Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates National Energy Dominance Month, 2025, and specifies October 2025 as the observance period. It emphasizes the long-standing role of domestic energy resources—including oil, coal, minerals, and natural gas—in supporting the United States’ economy, security, and prosperity. The proclamation invites government agencies, organizations, and the public to observe the month with appropriate programs and activities that highlight energy production, resilience, and innovation, and to recognize the importance of responsible management of energy resources. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-energy-dominance-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-energy-dominance-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Cybersecurity Awareness Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating National Cybersecurity Awareness Month for 2025 and reaffirming the Administration's commitment to strengthening the nation's cybersecurity to improve American lives, defend national sovereignty, and uphold the rights of American citizens, in response to evolving cybersecurity threats to national defense. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-cybersecurity-awareness-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-cybersecurity-awareness-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Adjusting Imports of Medium- and Heavy-Duty Vehicles, Vehicle Parts, and Buses into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation issued following a Department of Commerce investigation into whether imports of medium- and heavy-duty vehicles (MHDVs), their parts (MHDVPs), and buses affect national security. The proclamation implements adjustments to the import regime for these goods entering the United States, based on the identified national security findings and the Secretary of Commerce's report. The adjustments apply to specified classes of vehicles and components and establish the dates and mechanisms by which the measures take effect and are enforced. The action aims to address potential national security concerns arising from international imports as determined by the investigation and pursuant to applicable law. The proclamation notes the scope of the affected items and the regulatory framework governing the implementation and enforcement of the adjustments. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/adjusting-imports-of-medium-and-heavy-duty-vehicles-medium-and-heavy-duty-vehicle-parts-and-buses-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/adjusting-imports-of-medium-and-heavy-duty-vehicles-medium-and-heavy-duty-vehicle-parts-and-buses-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum for the Secretary of War and the Director of the Office of Management and Budget: Use of Available Department of War Funds for Military Pay and Allowances During Lapse in Annual Appropriations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum directs the use of available Department of War funds to cover military pay and allowances during a lapse in annual appropriations. It acknowledges that current appropriations have lapsed and clarifies the scope and purpose of using remaining funds to ensure continuation of compensation for military personnel during the lapse. The document outlines the intended application of funds, the authority under which expenditures may be made, and the expected duration and oversight associated with funding during the lapse. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing Federal Hiring Accountability and Workforce Management]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's constitutional and statutory authority, establishes policies and requirements to ensure accountability in federal hiring. It notes a past eight-month period during which the federal workforce was reduced and the administration aimed to improve the efficiency of government services, with a focus on prioritizing staffing in national security positions. The order directs federal agencies to implement hiring practices, oversight mechanisms, and reporting procedures intended to enhance transparency, streamline recruitment, and ensure staffing aligns with national security needs while continuing to manage workforce changes in a manner consistent with the stated objective of accountability. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/ensuring-continued-accountability-in-federal-hiring/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/ensuring-continued-accountability-in-federal-hiring/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Declaration on Enduring Peace and Prosperity]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House publishes a presidential action titled The Trump Declaration for Enduring Peace and Prosperity. The declaration announces the commitment by all involved parties to a peace agreement and describes it as a response to over two years of suffering and loss in the region. It outlines the objective of establishing a lasting framework to promote security and prosperity and characterizes the resulting period as a new chapter defined by hope and shared goals. The document states support for the agreement and for President Trump's leadership, and notes that signatories endorse the plan and its implementation as part of the pursuit of enduring peace and prosperity in the region. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/the-trump-declaration-for-enduring-peace-and-prosperity/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/the-trump-declaration-for-enduring-peace-and-prosperity/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>