<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 11:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patriot Day 2025 Proclamation Honoring the 24th Anniversary of the September 11 Attacks]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates September 11, 2025, as Patriot Day and National Day of Service and Remembrance, commemorating the 24th anniversary of the September 11 terrorist attacks and calling on Americans to observe the day with remembrance and acts of service. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum on Addressing Misleading Direct-To-Consumer Prescription Drug Advertisements and FDA Regulatory Authority]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential memorandum directs the Secretary of Health and Human Services and the Commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration to address issues arising from direct-to-consumer advertising of prescription drugs. The document notes that Congressional authority to regulate prescription drug advertising was established in 1962 and affirms the FDA's regulatory remit over such advertising. It highlights concerns that some DTC advertisements may misstate the risks and benefits of medications, encourage reliance on medications over lifestyle changes, potentially interfere with the physician-patient relationship, and disproportionately promote higher-cost drugs over cheaper options. The memorandum calls for a comprehensive review of current DTC advertising practices and consideration of steps within the FDA’s regulatory authority to improve accuracy, increase transparency, protect consumers, and align advertising standards with public health objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-for-the-secretary-of-health-and-human-services-the-commissioner-of-food-and-drugs/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-for-the-secretary-of-health-and-human-services-the-commissioner-of-food-and-drugs/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Restore the United States Department of War]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The document announces an executive action to restore the United States Department of War, a federal department historically responsible for managing the armed forces. It notes that the department was originally established on August 7, 1789 by President George Washington to oversee the operation and maintenance of the military. The order specifies the purpose of reestablishing the department within the executive branch, defines its general mandate related to defense administration and military affairs, and outlines the authority and organizational framework for its operation, including coordination with other national security and defense entities. The summary indicates the restoration is intended to reinstate governance structures that historically supported military operations, while maintaining consistency with current national security objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-the-united-states-department-of-war/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-the-united-states-department-of-war/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Modifying the Scope of Reciprocal Tariffs and Establishing Procedures for Implementing Trade and Security Agreements]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, the President issues actions that modify the scope of reciprocal tariffs and establish procedures for implementing trade and security agreements. The document cites the constitutional basis and statutory authorities and describes the intended adjustments to reciprocal tariff arrangements along with the administrative processes for implementing related trade and security measures. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/modifying-the-scope-of-reciprocal-tariffs-and-establishing-procedures-for-implementing-trade-and-security-agreements/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/modifying-the-scope-of-reciprocal-tariffs-and-establishing-procedures-for-implementing-trade-and-security-agreements/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Strengthening Efforts to Protect U.S. Nationals from Wrongful Detention Abroad]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This Presidential Order asserts the President's constitutional and statutory authority, including the Levinson Hostage Recovery and Hostage-Taking Accountability Act (22 U.S.C. 1741 et seq.), to strengthen government efforts to protect U.S. nationals from wrongful detention abroad. Section 1, titled Purpose, states that the United States must enhance its efforts in this area. The document signals a policy shift toward increasing protective measures for U.S. nationals detained overseas and relies on the Levinson Act as part of the legal framework for these actions. The excerpt provided does not detail the specific actions, agencies involved, or methods to be employed, but indicates an intent to implement measures consistent with the stated objective. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/strengthening-efforts-to-protect-u-s-nationals-from-wrongful-detention-abroad/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/strengthening-efforts-to-protect-u-s-nationals-from-wrongful-detention-abroad/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Commissioner of Labor Statistics, Federal Maritime Commissioner, and Assistant Secretary (Erwin Antoni, Laura DiBella, Steven Haines)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations to the Senate for three individuals: Erwin Antoni, of Pennsylvania, to be Commissioner of Labor Statistics, Department of Labor, for a four-year term, vice Erika L. McEntarfer; Laura DiBella, of Florida, to be Federal Maritime Commissioner for a term expiring June 30, 2028, vice L. E. Sola, term expired; and Steven Haines, of Virginia, to be an Assistant Secretary, with the department unspecified in the excerpt. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-f7c7/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-f7c7/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making Federal Architecture Beautiful Again]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential action emphasizing the Founders' regard for federal civic architecture and outlining the objective to improve the design and aesthetics of federal public buildings. The order directs relevant federal agencies to review current architectural policies and develop guidelines aimed at enhancing the appearance, dignity, and civic impact of federal architecture, while considering historical preservation and accessibility within the design process. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/making-federal-architecture-beautiful-again/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/making-federal-architecture-beautiful-again/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>