<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:00:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Daniel E. Burrows as Assistant Attorney General; Stevan Pearce as Director of the Bureau of Land Management; and Douglas Weaver as Nuclear Regulatory Commission Member]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced three nominations sent to the Senate. Daniel E. Burrows, of Colorado, is nominated to be an Assistant Attorney General, to fill the vacancy resulting from Aaron Reitz's resignation. Stevan Pearce, of New Mexico, is nominated to be Director of the Bureau of Land Management, to fill the vacancy resulting from Tracy Stone-Manning's resignation. Douglas Weaver, of Maryland, is nominated to be a Member of the Nuclear Regulatory Commission for the remainder of the term expiring June 30. These nominations are part of the administration's process for executive branch appointments requiring Senate confirmation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations to Senate for Commodity Futures Trading Commission Chair and Commissioner; Nomination Withdrawal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that the Senate will receive nominations for the Commodity Futures Trading Commission: Michael Selig of Florida to serve as Chairman, succeeding Rostin Behnam, and Michael Selig to serve as a Commissioner for a term expiring April 13, 2029, to fill the expired term of Christy Goldsmith Romero. Additionally, a nomination of Joel Rayburn was withdrawn and sent to the Senate. These announcements indicate changes in the leadership and membership of the CFTC and the withdrawal of a separate nomination from consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President on Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation discusses the role of copper in supporting the United States' energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors, noting copper's importance from the electric grid to semiconductors. It asserts that preserving and expanding domestic copper smelting capacity is essential to reduce reliance on foreign supply chains. It references regulatory relief for certain stationary sources as a policy measure intended to promote American mineral security, indicating that regulatory actions are being adjusted to support domestic mineral production and supply chain resilience. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara to be U.S. Ambassador to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jennifer Wicks McNamara, a resident of Virginia, has been nominated to serve as Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary of the United States to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The nomination has been sent to the United States Senate for consideration, initiating the confirmation process. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>