<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 11:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Navy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Navy. The text notes that the Navy traces its origins to the Second Continental Congress, which established a naval force that would evolve into the United States Navy. It acknowledges the service’s historical development and its role in national security, and calls for appropriate observances to mark the anniversary. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-navy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-navy/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[General Pulaski Memorial Day, 2025 Proclamation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In a presidential proclamation, the President designates General Pulaski Memorial Day for 2025 to honor Casimir Pulaski, a brigadier general who volunteered to support American independence in 1777 and is recognized as the "Soldier of Liberty" and the "Father of the American Cavalry." The proclamation invites Americans to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies, educational activities, and reflection on Pulaski's contributions to liberty and the development of the American Cavalry. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/general-pulaski-memorial-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/general-pulaski-memorial-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President Declaring National Breast Cancer Awareness Month]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating October as National Breast Cancer Awareness Month, recognizing the impact of breast cancer on individuals and families in the United States, and reaffirming the Administration's commitment to advancing research, promoting prevention and early detection, expanding access to high-quality treatment and care, and providing support to patients and their loved ones as part of a coordinated national effort. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/presidential-message-on-national-breast-cancer-awareness-month/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/presidential-message-on-national-breast-cancer-awareness-month/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Lee Lipton to serve as United States Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Republic of the Philippines]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Lee Lipton, a resident of Florida, has been nominated to serve as the United States Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Republic of the Philippines. The nomination has been sent to the United States Senate for confirmation. The position entails representing the United States in the Philippines and supervising the activities of the U.S. embassy and the conduct of diplomatic relations with the host nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-85f4/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-85f4/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Decision and Statement of Reasons Regarding the 2025 Ambler Road Appeal under ANILCA Section 1106(a) and Approval of AIDEA's 2016 Ambler Road Project Application]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The action communicates the President's decision to approve the appeal filed by the Alaska Industrial Development and Export Authority (AIDEA) under section 1106(a) of the Alaska National Interest Lands Conservation Act (ANILCA) and to approve AIDEA's 2016 revised consolidated application for the Ambler Road Project. The decision includes a statement of reasons describing the legal basis, objectives, and considerations that supported the approval, as explained in the accompanying documentation published by the White House. The official decision is posted on the White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/decision-of-the-president-and-statement-of-reasons-on-2025-ambler-road-appeal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/decision-of-the-president-and-statement-of-reasons-on-2025-ambler-road-appeal/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>