<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:00:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Granting Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation directs regulatory relief for certain stationary sources to support American mineral security, with emphasis on the role of copper in energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors. It highlights the importance of maintaining and increasing domestic copper smelting capacity to reduce reliance on foreign supply chains and to strengthen the resilience of supply chains for minerals critical to national interests. The proclamation describes the intended effect as facilitating regulatory relief for specified stationary sources to enhance domestic mineral production and processing, thereby contributing to overall American mineral security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara to be Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President has nominated Jennifer Wicks McNamara, of Virginia, to serve as the United States ambassador to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The nomination has been sent to the United States Senate for consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Day of Remembrance for Charlie Kirk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates a National Day of Remembrance in connection with the death of Charlie Kirk on September 10, 2025. The proclamation notes that the incident occurred on a campus courtyard and calls for nationwide observances and appropriate acknowledgments to honor Charlie Kirk's memory. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>