<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum NSPM-8: Policy Framework for United States Leadership in 6G Wireless Technology]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Directs and coordinates actions across multiple federal agencies and offices, including the State Department, Department of Defense, Department of Commerce, Department of Transportation, Department of Energy, Department of Homeland Security, the Office of Management and Budget, the Director of National Intelligence, the Federal Communications Commission, and senior White House policy officials, to advance United States leadership in sixth-generation (6G) wireless technology. The memorandum sets objectives to promote secure and resilient 6G supply chains, support research and development, establish standards, foster international partnerships, and safeguard national security and economic interests in 6G deployment and governance. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Bill of Rights Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President designates December 15, 2025 as Bill of Rights Day and highlights the historical origins of the United States’ founding principles, including sovereignty, justice, and self-government. The proclamation notes the ratification of the Bill of Rights and its enduring protections for individual rights, and it invites reflection on the rights guaranteed by the Constitution while encouraging appropriate observances and educational activities across federal agencies and the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designating Fentanyl as a Weapon of Mass Destruction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive action designating illicit fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction, explaining the policy rationale in Section 1 that fentanyl is closer to a chemical weapon than a narcotic, and referencing the use of very small quantities (two milligrams) as an illustrative threshold. The action establishes the framework for applying federal authorities in response to this threat. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Protect American Investors from Foreign-Owned and Politically Motivated Proxy Advisors]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued by the President under constitutional authority, addresses concerns that two foreign-owned proxy advisory firms, Institutional Shareholder Services Inc. and Glass, Lewis & Co., LLC, influence U.S. corporate governance policies and investor decision-making. The document notes the potential risks arising from foreign ownership and political motivation in proxy advice and directs federal agencies to evaluate the impact of such advisory services on American investors. The order aims to identify and pursue appropriate actions to safeguard investors, enhance transparency and accountability of proxy advisory firms, and ensure that investor guidance aligns with U.S. governance standards without undue foreign influence. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing a National Policy Framework for Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action asserts the President's constitutional and statutory authority to issue an order establishing a national policy framework for artificial intelligence. It states the purpose as advancing United States leadership in AI to strengthen national security, economic security, and competitive standing across multiple domains. The document references Section 1: Purpose and cites Executive Order 14179 of January 23 as its legal basis, indicating an intent to pursue a coordinated national AI policy framework in alignment with prior policy developments. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>