<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominees to the Senate for U.S. Attorney (District of Nevada), Assistant Secretary of State for Educational and Cultural Affairs, and Assistant Secretary of the Interior]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that nominations have been sent to the Senate for several senior executive appointments. The individuals named in the excerpt are George Kelesis, of Nevada, to be United States Attorney for the District of Nevada for a four-year term, replacing Jason M. Frierson; Catherine Dillon, of Maryland, to be Assistant Secretary of State for Educational and Cultural Affairs, replacing Lee Satterfield; and William Hague, of Washington, to be Assistant Secretary of the Interior. The release notes that additional nominations are included in the same post, which is titled Nominations Sent to the Senate and was published on the White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening United States National Defense Through Clean Coal Power Generation Fleet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This White House presidential action describes objectives to ensure the electric grid remains resilient and reliable for military installations, operations, and defense-industrial production, and to avoid reliance on intermittent energy sources. It notes that the grid is foundational to national defense and economic stability, and outlines policy directions intended to address prolonged energy disruptions by leveraging a clean coal power generation fleet, thereby supporting national defense and economic resilience. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Addressing Threats to the United States by the Government of Iran under IEEPA and Related Authorities]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action asserts the President's authority under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, and section 301 of related statutes to address threats posed by the Government of Iran. The action describes potential measures and authorizes relevant agencies to implement policy actions and enforcement mechanisms as necessary to protect national security, economic stability, and foreign policy interests of the United States. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Black History Month, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating February 2026 as National Black History Month. The proclamation references the 250th anniversary of American independence and acknowledges the contributions of Black Americans to the nation’s history over more than two and a half centuries, highlighting their roles as part of the nation’s historical narrative. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>