<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Semiconductors, Semiconductor Manufacturing Equipment, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation, issued under section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, relies on a report transmitted by the Secretary of Commerce to the President on December 22, 2025, assessing the national-security effects of imports of semiconductors, semiconductor manufacturing equipment, and their derivative products. The proclamation orders adjustments to the import regime for these items into the United States to address the findings of that report. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a Second Emergency Board to Investigate Disputes Between the Long Island Rail Road Company and Employees Represented by Labor Organizations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced the establishment of a second emergency board under the Railway Labor Act to investigate disputes between the Long Island Rail Road Company and certain of its employees represented by labor organizations, including the Transportation Communications Union, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Adjusting Imports of Processed Critical Minerals and Their Derivative Products into the United States Under Section 232]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On October 24, 2025, the Secretary of Commerce transmitted to the President a report examining the national security effects of imports of processed critical minerals and their derivative products (PCMDPs). In response, the President issued a proclamation adjusting imports of PCMDPs and their derivative products into the United States, under section 232. The proclamation outlines the scope of the adjustments, applicable effective dates, and any transitional or compliance provisions, and directs relevant federal agencies to implement the measures. The actions are intended to address the national security concerns identified in the report and to support the resilience of critical mineral supply chains. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Safeguard Venezuelan Oil Revenue for the Benefit of the American and Venezuelan People]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive order asserts authority under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act (IEEPA) and the National Emergencies Act (NEA), along with section 301 of title 3, United States Code, to authorize actions aimed at safeguarding revenue from Venezuelan oil. The order identifies the legal basis, outlines the scope of powers to be utilized, and describes the objective of protecting oil-related revenue for the benefit of both the American and Venezuelan people. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Pursuant to the Defense Production Act Regarding the Acquisition of Certain Emcore Corporation Assets by Hiefo Corporation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's authority and Section 721 of the Defense Production Act of 1950, directs actions related to the acquisition of certain assets of Emcore Corporation by Hiefo Corporation. It includes findings stating there is credible evidence related to the matter and establishes the framework for further steps or actions under the Defense Production Act to address the acquisition. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>