<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 11:00:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum for the Attorney General and United States Attorney for the District of Columbia Regarding Enforcement of Death Penalty Laws in the District of Columbia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential memorandum directs the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia to enforce federal death penalty laws within the District of Columbia. It references the President's constitutional and statutory authority and assigns responsibilities to relevant federal officials to coordinate enforcement efforts, outline procedures for pursuing federal capital prosecutions, and ensure that federal capital punishment statutes are applied in the District to deter and punish the most serious crimes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025, to honor the sacrifices of Gold Star mothers and families of service members who died in the line of duty, and to encourage appropriate observances and recognition across federal agencies and the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Implementing Provisions of the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order authorizes regulatory actions under the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (Public Law 118-50, Division H) to regulate foreign adversary controlled applications. It references Section 1, Background, which defines foreign adversary controlled applications and identifies TikTok as a primary example, and outlines the statutory basis and objectives for safeguarding national security through regulatory measures affecting these applications. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Restricting Entry of Certain Nonimmigrant Workers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation restricts the entry of certain nonimmigrant workers into the United States and references concerns that the H-1B visa program has been used to replace American workers with lower-paid, lower-skilled labor. It describes displacement of American workers as a result of large-scale nonimmigrant visa use and outlines restrictions intended to protect the domestic labor market. The action is issued by the President as an executive measure addressing admissions of nonimmigrant workers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation designates National POW/MIA Recognition Day for 2025 and calls on the nation to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies and activities. It honors United States Armed Forces members who were prisoners of war or who are missing in action, acknowledges the enduring uncertainty faced by their families, and reaffirms the government's commitment to accountability, recovery efforts, and dignified remembrance. The proclamation notes the long history of service and sacrifice across conflicts from the Revolutionary War to present-day events, and it encourages federal, state, local, tribal governments and the American people to observe the day and support efforts to account for missing personnel. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Immigration Policy Reversal and Administrative Procedures]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued by the President under constitutional and statutory authority, states the administration’s intent to reverse certain immigration policies implemented by the prior administration and to address the resulting increase in immigrant arrivals. The order describes the purpose of the action, outlines the rationale for changing policy, and provides a framework for revising guidelines and procedures related to the review, evaluation, and processing of immigration requests, including the scope and anticipated implementation of the policy changes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>