<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:00:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing the General Terms of the United States of America-United Kingdom Economic Prosperity Deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action implements the agreed-upon general terms of the economic partnership between the United States and the United Kingdom. It is based on the authority granted to the President under the Constitution and various laws, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962. The implementation details and specific measures are not specified in the provided excerpt. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Permit for the Expansion and Operation of a Vehicular Border Crossing at the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge Land Port of Entry]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President of the United States authorized the City of Laredo, Texas, to expand, maintain, and operate a vehicular crossing at the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge land port of entry, subject to specified conditions, to facilitate border crossing activities between the United States and Mexico. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>