<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:00:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing the General Terms of the United States of America-United Kingdom Economic Prosperity Deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The order authorizes the implementation of the agreed-upon general terms of the economic arrangement between the United States of America and the United Kingdom, establishing procedures for the execution of the deal consistent with applicable laws and authorities, including relevant statutes governing emergency economic powers and trade measures. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Permit for the Expansion and Operation of the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge Land Border Crossing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President authorized the City of Laredo, Texas, to expand, maintain, and operate a vehicular border crossing at the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge Land Port of Entry, subject to specified conditions. This permit allows ongoing use and potential expansion of the land port of entry to facilitate border crossings. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>