<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation Adjusting Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States under a Section 232 National Security Investigation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation states that on July 1, 2025, the Secretary of Commerce transmitted a report examining the effects of imports of timber, lumber, and their derivative products (collectively wood products) on the national security of the United States under section 232. Based on the findings in that report, the President is implementing measures to adjust imports of these wood products into the United States. The action follows the ongoing Section 232 national security review and is reflected in a September 2025 presidential action notice published by the White House. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on the Continuance of Certain Federal Advisory Committees]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority vested in the President by the Constitution and United States law, and in accordance with chapter 10 of title 5, United States Code (the Federal Advisory Committee Act), this order continues the existence of the advisory committees listed in Section 1 through September 30, 2027. Section 1 states that each advisory committee listed is continued until that date, with subsection (a) identifying the specific committees. The action preserves the ongoing operation of these federal advisory committees as authorized by statute. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum for the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia: Enforcing the Death Penalty Laws in the District of Columbia to Deter and Punish the Most Heinous Crimes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential memorandum directs the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia to enforce the federal death penalty within the District of Columbia for the most serious offenses, citing constitutional and statutory authority, and outlines intended actions to deter and punish those crimes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President of the United States: Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025, as an annual observance to honor the families of service members who died in the line of duty. The proclamation acknowledges the sacrifices of fallen service members and expresses gratitude to Gold Star families, and it urges government and civilian communities to observe the day with appropriate recognition and remembrance. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Regulating Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Under Public Law 118-50, Division H, with Focus on TikTok]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order asserts presidential authority under the Constitution and federal law to regulate foreign adversary controlled applications as defined in Public Law 118-50, Division H (the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act). The order identifies TikTok and related applications as primary subjects and establishes the policy objective of protecting national security by applying regulatory measures to such applications. It directs relevant executive departments and agencies to implement the provisions of the Act and to address associated risks through governance, security safeguards, and risk-management actions, as part of a broader effort to mitigate potential threats posed by foreign adversary controlled applications. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>