<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 15:00:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of the National Energy Dominance Council]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes the National Energy Dominance Council, aimed at promoting the United States' natural resources and leadership in energy technologies. The Council's purpose is to advance policies that enhance the nation's energy security and economic prosperity through strategic innovation in energy production and resource management. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/establishing-the-national-energy-dominance-council/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/establishing-the-national-energy-dominance-council/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Submitted to the Senate for Various Department Positions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This document details the nominations sent to the Senate for confirmation of several individuals to key positions within the federal government. The nominees include Gary Andres from Virginia for the role of Assistant Secretary of Health and Human Services, Daniel Aronowitz from Virginia for Assistant Secretary of Labor, James Baehr from Louisiana for the position of General Counsel at the Department of Veterans Affairs, and Kirsten Baesler from North Dakota for Assistant Secretary for Elementary and Secondary Education, among others. Each nomination is a step in the process of appointing officials to leadership roles in these departments. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Aluminum into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation addresses the findings of a report submitted by the Secretary of Commerce regarding the impact of aluminum imports on the national security of the United States, in accordance with Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962. The report was transmitted on January 19, 2018, and initiates a review of aluminum import policies to determine necessary adjustments aimed at safeguarding national security interests. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/adjusting-imports-of-aluminum-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/adjusting-imports-of-aluminum-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Announcement of Members for the President's Intelligence Advisory Board]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President has announced the appointment of a new group of individuals to serve on the President's Intelligence Advisory Board (PIAB). This board is intended to provide advice to the President regarding critical national security issues, focusing on the effectiveness of the Intelligence Community in alignment with the current administration's policies. The appointed members are recognized for their expertise and experience in intelligence and security matters. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-the-presidents-intelligence-advisory-board/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-the-presidents-intelligence-advisory-board/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Steel into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation addresses the conclusion of negotiations and agreements with various countries, including Argentina and Australia, regarding the importation of steel into the United States. It outlines the adjustments made to the import policies and sets the framework for ongoing discussions with other nations on similar trade matters. The proclamation serves to inform interested parties of the changes implemented in relation to steel imports. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/adjusting-imports-of-steel-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/adjusting-imports-of-steel-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporarily Suspending Enforcement of the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act for Economic and National Security Review]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This Presidential Executive Order outlines the decision to pause the enforcement of the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act (FCPA), which has been in effect since 1977. The order cites the need to evaluate the implications of the FCPA on American economic interests and national security. It establishes a framework for reviewing the enforcement practices related to the FCPA, with the intent to assess its impact on U.S. businesses and international trade relations going forward. The order emphasizes a commitment to balancing anti-corruption efforts with the enhancement of the nation's economic and security priorities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/pausing-foreign-corrupt-practices-act-enforcement-to-further-american-economic-and-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/pausing-foreign-corrupt-practices-act-enforcement-to-further-american-economic-and-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>