<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Address Competition in the Residential Real Estate Market Involving Institutional Investors and Individual Homebuyers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to assess and address practices by large institutional investors in the residential housing market that may affect competition and access for individual homebuyers. The objective is to promote fair competition in the purchase of single-family homes and support housing affordability. The order outlines steps such as data collection and reporting on investor activity, evaluating potential regulatory or policy actions, and coordinating with relevant agencies to mitigate advantages used by institutional buyers that could limit opportunities for main street homebuyers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/stopping-wall-street-from-competing-with-main-street-homebuyers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/stopping-wall-street-from-competing-with-main-street-homebuyers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation designating National Day of Patriotic Devotion, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating National Day of Patriotic Devotion for 2026. The proclamation requests appropriate observances by federal agencies and calls on the American people to participate in ceremonies and activities that reflect on national identity and core civic values. It describes the observance as a formal occasion to acknowledge national sovereignty, public safety, and the rule of law, and to recognize the roles of citizens and public servants in supporting national unity and civic life. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/national-day-of-patriotic-devotion-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/national-day-of-patriotic-devotion-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Religious Freedom Day, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates Religious Freedom Day, 2026, and notes the United States' 250-year history of recognizing the right to freely practice religion, to follow one's conscience, and to worship without fear. It describes these freedoms as essential rights and affirms the nation's ongoing commitment to protecting religious liberty for individuals and communities nationwide. The proclamation emphasizes the importance of observing Religious Freedom Day and invites reflection on the role of religious liberty as a foundational element of the nation's identity. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/religious-freedom-day-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/religious-freedom-day-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Adjusting Imports of Semiconductors, Semiconductor Manufacturing Equipment, and Their Derivative Products Into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Presidential proclamation issued pursuant to Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, based on a report from the Secretary of Commerce transmitted on December 22, 2025, regarding the effects of imports of semiconductors, semiconductor manufacturing equipment, and related derivative products on U.S. national security. The proclamation directs adjustments to imports of these items into the United States to address the national security concerns identified in the report. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-semiconductors-semiconductor-manufacturing-equipment-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a Second Emergency Board to Investigate Disputes Between the Long Island Rail Road Company and Certain of Its Employees Represented by Certain Labor Organizations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President established a second Emergency Board under the Railway Labor Act to investigate and report on disputes involving the Long Island Rail Road Company and certain employees who are represented by specified labor organizations. The Board is authorized to conduct investigations and hearings, gather relevant information, and prepare findings and recommendations to facilitate resolution of the disputes and to assist in preventing or shortening any potential disruption to rail service. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/establishing-a-second-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Processed Critical Minerals and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation announcing adjustments to the import policy for processed critical minerals and their derivative products into the United States in response to a national security assessment conducted under section 232. The assessment's report was transmitted to the President by the Secretary of Commerce on October 24, 2025, detailing the potential national security impacts of these imports. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/adjusting-imports-of-processed-critical-minerals-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Safeguard Venezuelan Oil Revenue Under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order asserts authorities under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act to safeguard revenue generated from Venezuela's oil sector. It implements measures that restrict certain financial transactions and block assets connected to the Venezuelan government and related parties. The order directs federal agencies to implement and enforce these restrictions, monitor the flow of oil revenue, and coordinate with international partners to prevent diversion or misappropriation of revenue, with the aim of protecting the economic interests of the American and Venezuelan people. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/safeguarding-venezuelan-oil-revenue-for-the-good-of-the-american-and-venezuelan-people/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>