<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 12:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation designating Anti-Communism Week, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating Anti-Communism Week for 2025, announcing an observance to reflect on the impact of communism and remember losses attributed to regimes associated with the ideology, including references to substantial loss of life. The proclamation encourages reflection on historical consequences and remembrance of victims. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Assistant Attorney General, Bureau of Land Management Director, and Nuclear Regulatory Commission Member]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This White House entry lists nominations sent to the Senate for three positions: Daniel E. Burrows to serve as Assistant Attorney General (to succeed Aaron Reitz); Stevan Pearce to serve as Director of the Bureau of Land Management (to succeed Tracy Stone-Manning); and Douglas Weaver to serve as a Commissioner on the Nuclear Regulatory Commission for the remainder of the term expiring June 30. The page is part of the President's nominations to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations to Senate for Michael Selig as CFTC Chairman and Commissioner; Withdrawal of Joel Rayburn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The post announces nominations sent to the Senate for Michael Selig, of Florida, to be Chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, to replace Rostin Behnam, and to be a Commissioner of the CFTC for a term expiring April 13, 2029, to replace Christy Goldsmith Romero. It also notes a withdrawal sent to the Senate for Joel Rayburn. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Providing Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation emphasizes the importance of copper and other minerals to the United States’ energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors. It provides regulatory relief for certain stationary sources as a means to promote American mineral security and reduce reliance on foreign supply chains, with the goal of expanding and safeguarding domestic mineral production capacity, including copper smelting and processing. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>