<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:00:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Implementing the United States–Japan Agreement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's constitutional and statutory authorities, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962, implements the United States–Japan Agreement. It authorizes and governs measures necessary to carry out the terms of the bilateral arrangement, and sets forth the authorities and actions available to implement, enforce, and adjust related economic and trade policies in accordance with the agreement. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/implementing-the-united-states-japan-agreement/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/implementing-the-united-states-japan-agreement/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Tammy Bruce to serve as Deputy Representative of the United States to the United Nations with ambassadorial rank, and as Deputy Representative to the United Nations Security Council]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for Tammy Bruce of California to serve as Deputy Representative of the United States to the United Nations with the rank and status of Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary, and to serve concurrently as the Deputy Representative to the United Nations Security Council. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>