<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:00:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Admission Standards and National Security Concerns at Harvard University]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation by the President of the United States outlines the conditions under which admission to U.S. institutions of higher education is granted to foreign nationals. It emphasizes that such admission is contingent upon the institution's adherence to federal laws and regulations. The proclamation specifically addresses national security considerations related to Harvard University and articulates the government's expectations regarding compliance from educational institutions that host foreign individuals for research, teaching, or study purposes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/enhancing-national-security-by-addressing-risks-at-harvard-university/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/enhancing-national-security-by-addressing-risks-at-harvard-university/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum on the Review of Presidential Actions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum, issued by the President of the United States, outlines the directive to review certain actions undertaken by the executive branch. It emphasizes the role of the President as the head of the executive branch and establishes guidelines for the review process of presidential actions to ensure they align with constitutional and legal standards. The document seeks input from the Attorney General and the Counsel to the President regarding this review. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/reviewing-certain-presidential-actions/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/reviewing-certain-presidential-actions/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Entry Restrictions for National Security and Public Safety]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation outlines the continuation of entry restrictions for foreign nationals into the United States, aimed at mitigating national security threats and enhancing public safety. It references the previous measures implemented during the President's first administration, including Executive Order 14161 issued on January 20, 2025, which was designed to address risks associated with foreign nationals. The proclamation emphasizes its foundation in legal support from the Supreme Court regarding these measures. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/restricting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-united-states-from-foreign-terrorists-and-other-national-security-and-public-safety-threats/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/restricting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-united-states-from-foreign-terrorists-and-other-national-security-and-public-safety-threats/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>