<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 11:00:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Restricting Entry of Certain Nonimmigrant Workers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation restricting entry of certain nonimmigrant workers into the United States. The proclamation notes that the H-1B nonimmigrant visa program was created to bring temporary high skilled workers to perform additive labor, but has been used in ways that replace American workers with lower paid, lower skilled labor. The objective of the proclamation is to protect American workers and maintain wage and labor market integrity by limiting entry for specific nonimmigrant categories and directing federal agencies to implement and enforce the restrictions. The document outlines the scope of the restrictions and the administrative steps for enforcement, reflecting a policy recalibration of entry requirements for nonimmigrant workers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates National POW/MIA Recognition Day for 2025 and honors United States service members who were prisoners of war or are missing in action. It designates observance of the day, encourages the display of the POW/MIA flag at federal buildings and in other appropriate locations, and reaffirms the government's commitment to accounting for missing personnel and to providing information and support to their families. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order The Gold Card: Policy Changes Regarding Immigration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order asserts the president's authority to implement changes to immigration policy and sets forth the administration's aim to revise immigration policies instituted by the prior administration. The document indicates a focus on addressing how immigrants are admitted and processed and describes a purpose section outlining the administration's goals to modify the previous policy framework as part of ongoing executive actions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoring Law and Order in Memphis: Presidential Memorandum Directing Interagency Coordination]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential memorandum addressed to top federal officials directs interagency coordination to address public safety concerns in Memphis. It instructs the Secretary of the Treasury, Secretary of War, Attorney General, and the Secretaries of Health and Human Services, Housing and Urban Development, Transportation, Homeland Security, along with the Directors of the U.S. Marshals Service and the FBI, among others, to assess conditions, coordinate with state and local authorities, and take actions to support law enforcement, public safety, and emergency response in Memphis. The memorandum outlines frameworks for rapid interagency collaboration, resource deployment, and monitoring of public safety measures to restore order in the city. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-law-and-order-in-memphis/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restoring-law-and-order-in-memphis/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patriot Day 2025 Proclamation Designating September 11, 2025 as Patriot Day]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates September 11, 2025 as Patriot Day and calls upon the American people to observe a moment of remembrance at 8:46 a.m. local time to honor the victims of the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks and to recognize the service of first responders and others affected by the attacks. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/patriot-day-2025-the-24th-annivresary-of-the-september-11-terrorist-attacks/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>