<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:00:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designation of Antifa as a Domestic Terrorist Organization]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action designates Antifa as a domestic terrorist organization under applicable law. The accompanying section describes Antifa as an organization that advocates violent action against the United States government and law enforcement and coordinates a nationwide campaign using illegal means. The White House publication provides the designation and outlines related legal authorities and enforcement considerations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/designating-antifa-as-a-domestic-terrorist-organization/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/designating-antifa-as-a-domestic-terrorist-organization/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President: National Hispanic Heritage Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating National Hispanic Heritage Month for the year 2025. The proclamation acknowledges the contributions of Hispanic-American citizens, past and present, and describes their impact on American society. It highlights the resilience, spirit, and commitment of Hispanic-American communities to shared American values. The document notes that Hispanic-American patriots have served on the front lines of the U.S. military, among other forms of public service, and it calls for reflection, education, and celebration during the designated period. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-hispanic-heritage-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-hispanic-heritage-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Constitution Week, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This document is a presidential proclamation designating Constitution Week, 2025 to commemorate the 238th anniversary of the signing of the United States Constitution and to reaffirm the nation's commitment to the Constitution as the framework for self-government, the rule of law, and civic responsibility. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/constitution-week-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/constitution-week-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memorandum of Understanding Between the Government of the United States of America and the Government of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland Regarding the Technology Prosperity Deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum establishes a bilateral framework for cooperation between the United States and the United Kingdom to advance joint initiatives under the Technology Prosperity Deal. The agreement outlines objectives related to science and technology capabilities, standards development, and collaborative activities intended to promote innovation, economic growth, and resilience, and to coordinate related governance and policy considerations across the two governments. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-of-understanding-between-the-government-of-the-united-states-of-america-and-the-government-of-the-united-kingdom-of-great-britain-and-northern-ireland-regarding-the-technology-prosperity-de/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/memorandum-of-understanding-between-the-government-of-the-united-states-of-america-and-the-government-of-the-united-kingdom-of-great-britain-and-northern-ireland-regarding-the-technology-prosperity-de/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing An Emergency Board to Investigate Disputes Between the Long Island Rail Road Company and Certain of Its Employees Represented by Certain Labor Organizations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Summary: This presidential action establishes an Emergency Board under the Railway Labor Act to examine and report on disputes between the Long Island Rail Road Company and certain employees represented by specified labor organizations. The Board is authorized to receive evidence, hear issues, and issue findings and recommendations to help resolve the disputes. The labor organizations associated with these disputes include the Transportation Communications Union, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Trainmen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, among others. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/establishing-an-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/establishing-an-emergency-board-to-investigate-disputes-between-the-long-island-rail-road-company-and-certain-of-its-employees-represented-by-certain-labor-organizations/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Extending the TikTok Enforcement Delay Under the 2025 Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action prolongs the enforcement delay described in section 2(a) of Executive Order 14166, issued January 20, 2025, which relates to applying the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act to TikTok. The president exercises authority to extend the period during which enforcement actions are postponed, specifying the new duration or date for the extension as outlined in the order. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/further-extending-the-tiktok-enforcement-delay-9dde/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/further-extending-the-tiktok-enforcement-delay-9dde/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for United States Attorney Positions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations to the United States Senate for several United States Attorney positions. The nominees include William Boyle, of North Carolina, to serve as United States Attorney for the Eastern District of North Carolina for a term of four years; Erin Creegan, of New Hampshire, to serve as United States Attorney for the District of New Hampshire for a term of four years; and Zachary Keller, of Louisiana, to serve as United States Attorney for a district in Louisiana for a term of four years. The notices indicate these are four-year terms and that the nominations have been sent to the Senate for consideration and confirmation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-5188/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-5188/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>