<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate: Tammy Bruce for Deputy Representative of the United States to the United Nations and Deputy Representative to the UN Security Council, with the rank of Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Tammy Bruce of California has been nominated to serve as the Deputy Representative of the United States to the United Nations, with the rank and status of Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary, and as the Deputy Representative of the United States to the United Nations Security Council. The nomination also provides for concurrent service in an additional capacity without additional compensation, the details of which are not specified in the excerpt. The nominations were sent to the Senate for its advice and consent. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-8a96/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President Honoring the Victims of the Tragedy in Minneapolis, Minnesota]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation issued by the President of the United States to honor and express respect for the victims of the violence that occurred on August 27, 2025, in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The proclamation cites the President's constitutional and legal authority and marks the occasion with an official observance of the loss and a formal expression of sympathy on behalf of the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/honoring-the-victims-of-the-tragedy-in-minneapolis-minnesota/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/honoring-the-victims-of-the-tragedy-in-minneapolis-minnesota/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>