<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Adjusting Rates of Basic Pay for Statutory Pay Systems]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued by the President under the Constitution and federal law, directs adjustments to the rates of basic pay or salaries for the statutory pay systems as defined in title 5 of the United States Code (5 U.S.C. 5302(1)). The adjustments are made pursuant to 5 U.S.C. 5303 and apply to employees covered by statutory pay systems. The order specifies the updated pay scales and subjects to which the changes apply, establishing the revised rates as part of the administration of federal compensation. The document cites the statutory authorities and formalizes the rate adjustments within the framework of federal pay administration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Advance United States Space Capabilities and Ensure Space Superiority]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to coordinate policy, programs, and investments to advance United States space capabilities and achieve space superiority. It outlines objectives to enhance national security, economic competitiveness, and technological leadership by expanding space-based infrastructure, research and development, and interagency collaboration. It emphasizes alignment of space-related activities across the executive branch to maintain advantages in space security, exploration, and utilization. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Closing Federal Departments and Agencies on December 24, 2025, and December 26, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under presidential authority, this executive action directs that all executive departments and agencies of the Federal Government shall be closed and their employees excused from duty on Wednesday, December 24, 2025, and Friday, December 26, 2025. The order establishes the dates for temporary government closure and requires agencies to implement the closure in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Expand Medical Marijuana and Cannabidiol Research]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues an executive order establishing a policy to broaden federal support for medical marijuana and cannabidiol (CBD) research. Building on a 2023 FDA review, the order directs federal agencies to enhance research infrastructure, facilitate clinical studies, and coordinate interagency efforts to advance medical treatments. The document emphasizes that Americans should have access to high-quality medical treatments and robust research capabilities, and it outlines steps to promote collaboration among federal, academic, and industry partners, expand funding opportunities, and improve data sharing and reporting on progress. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/increasing-medical-marijuana-and-cannabidiol-research/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/increasing-medical-marijuana-and-cannabidiol-research/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Restricting and Limiting the Entry of Foreign Nationals to Protect the Security of the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action describes restrictions on entry into the United States for certain foreign nationals aimed at addressing national security and public safety concerns. It notes that the Supreme Court upheld similar restrictions and states that the administration reinstated these policies through Executive Order 14161 on January 20, 2025. The action outlines the scope of the entry restrictions and their enforcement, and references continued use of these measures to protect the security of the United States. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/restricting-and-limiting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-security-of-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/restricting-and-limiting-the-entry-of-foreign-nationals-to-protect-the-security-of-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Address Price-Fixing and Anti-Competitive Practices in the U.S. Food Supply Chain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to identify and mitigate risks to national and economic security arising from price-fixing and anti-competitive behavior in the United States food supply chain. It notes that an affordable and secure food supply is vital to national security and the economy, and it highlights concerns about anti-competitive conduct, including actions by foreign-controlled corporations. The order requires interagency assessment of market practices, evaluation of existing laws and regulatory authorities, and development of actions to strengthen supply-chain resilience, promote competitive markets, protect critical food infrastructure, and enhance price transparency. It establishes processes for coordinated reporting, sets out milestones for policy development, and seeks to implement measures that reduce vulnerabilities in the food supply chain while maintaining access to affordable food for consumers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/addressing-security-risks-from-price-fixing-and-anti-competitive-behavior-in-the-food-supply-chain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/addressing-security-risks-from-price-fixing-and-anti-competitive-behavior-in-the-food-supply-chain/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>