<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential permit for the expansion and operation of the Camino Real border crossing in Eagle Pass, Texas]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive decision authorizes the City of Eagle Pass, Texas, to expand and maintain the existing vehicular and pedestrian crossing at the Camino Real International Bridge, allowing continued operation of this border crossing facility subject to specified conditions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of the United States-United Kingdom Economic Prosperity Agreement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action authorizes the implementation of the general terms outlined in the economic prosperity agreement between the United States and the United Kingdom. It is carried out under the authority of the Constitution and various statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962. The action formalizes the steps necessary to execute the agreed-upon measures aimed at fostering economic cooperation and prosperity between the two nations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>