<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum NSPM-8 on Advancing 6G Wireless Technology]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A National Security Presidential Memorandum (NSPM-8) issued by the President directing U.S. federal agencies to coordinate and implement actions to advance sixth-generation (6G) wireless technology. The memorandum identifies national security and economic goals for maintaining U.S. leadership in 6G, outlines policy actions to foster secure and resilient 6G networks, promotes collaboration with industry, academia, and international partners, and establishes oversight, reporting, and resource allocation mechanisms to monitor progress and ensure implementation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation designating Bill of Rights Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims December 15, 2025 as Bill of Rights Day, commemorating the historical ratification of the Bill of Rights and reaffirming the nation's commitment to civil liberties and the rule of law. The proclamation notes the Bill of Rights serves to limit governmental power and protect individual rights, and it urges federal agencies, state and local governments, educational institutions, and the public to observe the day through appropriate programs, education, and reflection on the core liberties guaranteed by the Constitution. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Declaring Fentanyl as a Weapon of Mass Destruction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order designates illicit fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction for policy and enforcement purposes. It includes Section 1, titled Purpose and Policy, which states that illicit fentanyl is closer to a chemical weapon than a narcotic. The document notes that two milligrams constitutes a trace amount, illustrating the scale of the drug's potential impact. The order establishes the rationale for treating fentanyl under a weapon-of-mass-destruction framework and outlines the intended policy direction for federal agencies to address its illicit manufacture, distribution, and use. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Protecting American Investors from Foreign-Owned and Politically-Motivated Proxy Advisors]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to assess the influence of foreign-owned proxy advisory firms on U.S. investors and corporate governance. It outlines steps to promote transparency and accountability in proxy voting advice, and to consider actions to mitigate reliance on such firms by American investors. The measures are intended to safeguard the interests of American investors and ensure that proxy recommendations are independent and accurate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing a National Policy Framework for Artificial Intelligence and Addressing State-Law Obstruction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes a national policy framework for artificial intelligence, stating that United States leadership in AI is intended to promote national and economic security and maintain competitive advantage across multiple domains. It cites authority vested in the President and references an earlier executive order (Executive Order 14179) as a basis for implementing the policy. The document appears to address potential obstacles posed by state laws that could obstruct the national AI policy and outlines interagency coordination and actions to implement and enforce the national AI policy framework across federal agencies, aiming to reduce fragmentation and ensure a unified approach nationwide. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>