<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Restricting Entry of Certain Nonimmigrant Workers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation states that the H-1B nonimmigrant visa program was created to bring temporary, high-skilled workers to the United States but has been used to replace American workers with lower-paid, lower-skilled labor. It notes concerns about large-scale displacement of American workers by nonimmigrant workers and announces restrictions on the entry of certain nonimmigrant workers to address these concerns. The proclamation directs relevant federal agencies to implement and enforce these entry restrictions and to establish procedures for compliance, including potential exemptions or adaptations as provided by law. The action reflects an objective to protect domestic labor markets by adjusting entry policies for nonimmigrant workers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation designates National POW/MIA Recognition Day for 2025 and honors U.S. service members who were captured or are missing in action in conflicts from the Revolutionary War through contemporary operations. It designates official observances to reflect on their experiences, and it reiterates the government's commitment to accounting for missing personnel and to supporting their families and veterans. The proclamation urges federal agencies, military installations, and civilian communities to observe the day and to recognize the sacrifices made by prisoners of war and those missing in action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Immigration Policy Reform (The Gold Card)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive order states the administration's intent to reverse immigration policies implemented by the prior administration and to address the resulting large flow of immigrants. It outlines the objective to reform immigration policy and its administration, focusing on evaluating and adjusting related processes and requirements to reflect current objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/the-gold-card/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>