<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Addressing Threats to the United States by the Government of Iran]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President asserts authority under the Constitution and multiple statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and sections of the Trade Act of 1974 (including section 604 and section 301), to address threats posed by the Government of Iran to the United States. The action relies on these authorities to respond to actions by Iran that have implications for U.S. national security, foreign policy, or economy. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Black History Month, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims February 2026 as National Black History Month, recognizing the historical contributions of Black Americans to the United States and noting the 250th anniversary of the nation's independence, while highlighting the roles Black Americans have played over more than two centuries in shaping the country. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Recognizing the Contributions of American Motor Racing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action, issued by the President, begins with an assertion of the President's authority and includes a section labeled 'Purpose and Policy.' It acknowledges American motor racing, including INDYCAR, and notes the sport's history in the United States as well as the high speeds achieved by racing vehicles. The document establishes the formal purpose and policy related to American motor racing. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/celebrating-american-greatness-with-american-motor-racing/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/celebrating-american-greatness-with-american-motor-racing/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>