<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:00:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for U.S. Attorney for the District of Nevada and for Assistant Secretaries of State and Interior]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations to the Senate for three individuals: George Kelesis of Nevada to be United States Attorney for the District of Nevada for a four-year term, replacing Jason M. Frierson; Catherine Dillon of Maryland to be Assistant Secretary of State for Educational and Cultural Affairs, replacing Lee Satterfield; and William Hague of Washington to be Assistant Secretary of the Interior. The excerpt indicates there are additional nominations included in the list that are not shown here. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening United States National Defense through Clean Coal Power Generation Fleet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House presidential action document states that the United States must maintain a resilient and reliable electric grid that is not dependent on intermittent energy sources. It describes the grid as foundational to national defense and economic stability, noting that prolonged disruptions could affect military installations, defense operations, and defense-industrial production. The document proposes measures to strengthen national defense by expanding or leveraging a fleet of clean coal power generation facilities to enhance grid reliability and resilience. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Addressing Threats from the Government of Iran]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President asserts authority under the Constitution and the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, and section 301 to address threats attributed to the Government of Iran. The action describes the legal basis for measures taken or to be taken in response to these threats, and specifies the use of executive authorities consistent with these statutes. It indicates that the measures are part of ongoing U.S. policy to counter risks to national security and foreign policy, and may include sanctions, restrictions on economic activity, and other actions authorized by the cited laws. The summary notes that the action aligns with prior emergency declarations and relevant statutory authorities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Black History Month, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates National Black History Month for 2026. It notes the 250th anniversary of United States independence and highlights the contributions of Black Americans to the nation's history. The proclamation discusses the historical significance of Black Americans and calls for appropriate observances and reflection during February 2026. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/national-black-history-month-2026/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>