<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 12:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing the Genesis Mission to Advance Scientific Discovery and Technological Innovation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive order authorizes the launch of the Genesis Mission as a national initiative aimed at advancing scientific discovery and technological innovation. It frames the effort as part of maintaining United States leadership in global technology competition and places the initiative within the historical context of scientific progress contributing to American prosperity. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/launching-the-genesis-mission/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/launching-the-genesis-mission/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Designating Certain Muslim Brotherhood Chapters as Foreign Terrorist Organizations and Specially Designated Global Terrorists under the Immigration and Nationality Act and the International Emergency Economic Powers Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority of the Constitution and the laws of the United States, including the Immigration and Nationality Act and the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, this executive order designates certain Muslim Brotherhood chapters as Foreign Terrorist Organizations (FTOs) and as Specially Designated Global Terrorists (SDGTs). The designation enables the implementation of measures to restrict support, funding, and other dealings with the designated entities and directs U.S. government agencies to carry out these designations in accordance with applicable law. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/designation-of-certain-muslim-brotherhood-chapters-as-foreign-terrorist-organizations-and-specially-designated-global-terrorists/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/designation-of-certain-muslim-brotherhood-chapters-as-foreign-terrorist-organizations-and-specially-designated-global-terrorists/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying the Scope of Tariffs on the Government of Brazil]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President, acting under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and the Trade Act of 1974, issues an executive action that modifies the scope of tariffs applicable to transactions involving the Government of Brazil. The order directs relevant agencies to implement the revised tariff scope and to ensure compliance with the change, specifying the effective date and any related regulatory actions required to carry out the modification. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Modifying the Scope of the Reciprocal Tariff with Respect to Certain Agricultural Products]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order authorizes modifications to the scope of the reciprocal tariff applied to a defined set of agricultural products. It is issued under the President's authority as described in the Constitution and federal statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, as amended. The order specifies changes to which agricultural products fall within the reciprocal tariff framework and directs the implementation of these changes by the relevant executive branch offices. It establishes the legal basis, scope, and effective process for adjusting coverage under the reciprocal tariff. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President on Veterans Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation honors the courage, honor, and dedicated service of United States veterans and acknowledges that their sacrifices have sustained the Nation’s freedoms and way of life. It designates Veterans Day as a time to remember and reflect on veterans’ contributions and to observe national expressions of gratitude and appropriate observances. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation Honoring the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Marine Corps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation marks the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Marine Corps. It acknowledges the Marine Corps' long history in American service and describes its core values, including courage, discipline, and unity, from the nation's founding to the present. The proclamation notes the significance of the milestone and outlines observances and recognition by public and government institutions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>