<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying the Scope of the Reciprocal Tariff With Respect to Certain Agricultural Products]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority vested in the President by the U.S. Constitution and applicable statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, this action modifies the scope of the reciprocal tariff as it applies to certain agricultural products. The action delineates adjustments to the eligibility and coverage of agricultural items within the reciprocal tariff framework, thereby changing which products are subject to reciprocal tariff treatment and related regulatory requirements. The measure is part of the ongoing administration of trade policy concerning agricultural commodities and is intended to implement these authorities through defined policy changes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President of the United States: Veterans Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating November 11, 2025, as Veterans Day, honoring the service and sacrifices of United States military veterans, recognizing their role in defending the nation and safeguarding freedoms, and inviting federal, state, and local governments and the public to observe and participate in appropriate ceremonies and remembrance activities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Marine Corps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Marine Corps and acknowledges its two-and-a-half-century history of service, discipline, and unity in defending the Nation. It highlights the contributions of Marines and civilian personnel, honors their families, and encourages observances, educational programs, and public recognition of the Corps' history and ongoing mission to safeguard national security. It invites federal, state, and local governments, as well as the American people, to participate in ceremonies and educational initiatives that reflect on the Marine Corps' legacy and continued importance to national security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jared Isaacman to be Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jared Isaacman, a resident of Pennsylvania, has been nominated to serve as Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, to succeed Bill Nelson who resigned from the position. The nomination has been transmitted to the U.S. Senate for its advice and consent and awaits Senate consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Modifying Reciprocal Tariff Rates Under the U.S.–China Economic and Trade Arrangement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action modifies reciprocal tariff rates on goods traded between the United States and the People's Republic of China in alignment with the Economic and Trade Arrangement between the two nations. It cites authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, as amended. The order specifies the applicable tariff changes and their effective dates, implementing the reciprocal tariff framework established by the arrangement and applying the agreed-upon rates to affected goods. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Modifying Tariffs to Address the Synthetic Opioid Supply Chain in the People's Republic of China]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, this action authorizes modifications to existing duties on goods imported from the People's Republic of China. The objective is to address risks associated with the synthetic opioid supply chain linked to China by adjusting tariff rates and related enforcement measures. The action directs implementation and coordination among relevant federal agencies and informs importers of the revised duties. The measure is part of a broader policy to deter illicit production and trafficking of synthetic opioids and to support public health and national security objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>