<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara to be United States Ambassador to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam Sent to the Senate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced the nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara, of Virginia, to serve as the United States Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The nomination has been transmitted to the Senate for its consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation Declaring National Day of Remembrance for Charlie Kirk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation notes that on September 10, 2025, Charlie Kirk was assassinated in a campus courtyard. It designates a National Day of Remembrance to honor his memory and to invite nationwide observances, including public ceremonies and moments of reflection, in recognition of the incident and its impact on the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President on the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Navy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation commemorating the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Navy. The document references the Navy's origins in the actions of the Second Continental Congress, marking its creation as a standing maritime force, and notes the ongoing importance of the Navy to national security, maritime commerce, and national defense. The proclamation describes historical development, honors service members and civilian personnel, and affirms the government's intention to recognize the Navy's heritage while continuing to support its mission and leadership on the seas. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-navy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-navy/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Honoring General Casimir Pulaski Memorial Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates General Casimir Pulaski Memorial Day for 2025 and honors the life and contributions of Brigadier General Casimir Pulaski, a Polish nobleman known for his service in the American Revolutionary War and often described as the Father of the American Cavalry and the Soldier of Liberty. The proclamation notes Pulaski's leadership and sacrifice in support of American independence and calls on the people of the United States to observe the day with appropriate ceremonies and educational activities that reflect on his legacy, and to recognize the ongoing significance of liberty, democratic ideals, and the international friendship between the United States and Poland. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/general-pulaski-memorial-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/general-pulaski-memorial-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>