<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:00:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: Anti-Communism Week, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Presidential proclamation designating Anti-Communism Week for 2025, describing the observance as a time to reflect on the historical impact of communism worldwide and noting that regimes aligned with communist ideology have caused extensive harm and the deaths of more than 100 million people. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Assistant Attorney General, Director of the Bureau of Land Management, and Nuclear Regulatory Commission Member]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced three nominations sent to the Senate: Daniel E. Burrows (Colorado) to be Assistant Attorney General, replacing Aaron Reitz; Stevan Pearce (New Mexico) to be Director of the Bureau of Land Management, replacing Tracy Stone-Manning; and Douglas Weaver (Maryland) to be a Commissioner of the Nuclear Regulatory Commission for the remainder of the term expiring June 30. The announcement appears on the White House website in the Nominations Sent to the Senate page. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations to the Senate for Chairman and Commissioner of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission; Withdrawal of Nomination of Joel Rayburn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President transmitted to the Senate nominations of Michael Selig, of Florida, to be Chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, replacing Rostin Behnam, and to be a Commissioner of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission for a term expiring April 13, 2029, replacing Christy Goldsmith Romero. A withdrawal of Joel Rayburn's nomination was also transmitted to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation highlights copper as essential to the United States' energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors and notes copper's role in critical infrastructure from the electric grid to semiconductors. It states that maintaining and expanding domestic copper smelting capacity is vital to reducing dependence on foreign supply chains. To promote American mineral security, the proclamation provides regulatory relief for certain stationary sources, outlining the goal of facilitating domestic mineral production while preserving health, safety, and environmental protections. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara to be Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary of the United States to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jennifer Wicks McNamara, of Virginia, has been nominated to serve as the United States Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The nomination has been transmitted to the United States Senate for its advice and consent, as part of the presidential appointment process. The notice is titled Nomination Sent to the Senate on the White House website, indicating the formal step of sending the nomination to the Senate for consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>