<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations to the Senate: Michael Selig for CFTC Chairman and Commissioner; Withdrawal: Joel Rayburn]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations to the Senate for Michael Selig, of Florida, to be Chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, replacing Rostin Behnam, and to be a Commissioner of the CFTC for a term expiring April 13, 2029, replacing Christy Goldsmith Romero. The announcement also notes a withdrawal from consideration for Joel Rayburn. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation on Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Support American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation emphasizes the strategic importance of copper to the United States' energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors and identifies domestic copper smelting capacity as a priority for reducing reliance on foreign supply chains. It announces regulatory relief targeted at certain stationary sources to enhance American mineral security by supporting domestic copper production and strengthening supply resilience. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara, of Virginia, to be Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary of the United States to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jennifer Wicks McNamara, a resident of Virginia, has been nominated to serve as the United States ambassador extraordinary and plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, with the nomination transmitted to the Senate for its consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating National Day of Remembrance for Charlie Kirk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates a National Day of Remembrance to honor the memory of Charlie Kirk following his death on September 10, 2025, and directs nationwide observances and commemorative activities. The proclamation specifies the purpose of the day and encourages participation across the country. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>