<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:00:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Appointment of Alex Meyer as Deputy Assistant to the President and Director of the White House Office of Intergovernmental Affairs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Alex Meyer has been appointed to the position of Deputy Assistant to the President and Director of the White House Office of Intergovernmental Affairs. In this role, he will be responsible for overseeing the engagement and coordination between the federal government and state and local governments. Previously, Meyer worked as the Deputy Political Director for the Trump-Vance 2024 Campaign, where he managed campaign operations in key battleground states including Georgia, North Carolina, and Pennsylvania. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-appointments-to-the-white-house-office-of-intergovernmental-affairs/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-appointments-to-the-white-house-office-of-intergovernmental-affairs/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Federal Law Regarding Subsidization of Immigration Policies]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order states the intention to enforce existing federal laws relating to immigration and taxpayer funds, particularly as articulated in the Personal Responsibility and Work Opportunity Reconciliation Act of 1996. It outlines the purpose of the order, emphasizing the administration's policy to address and regulate the use of taxpayer resources in relation to illegal immigration, in accordance with legal frameworks set by past congressional acts. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/ending-taxpayer-subsidization-of-open-borders/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/ending-taxpayer-subsidization-of-open-borders/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>