<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:00:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Supporting and Enhancing State and Local Law Enforcement Operations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This Executive Order outlines the Administration's commitment to enhance the capabilities of state and local law enforcement agencies. It emphasizes the importance of a well-equipped police force for maintaining community safety and aims to provide support for law enforcement in their efforts to effectively pursue criminal activities and ensure the protection of citizens. The order sets forth specific policies and actions to enable law enforcement agencies to better serve their communities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/04/strengthening-and-unleashing-americas-law-enforcement-to-pursue-criminals-and-protect-innocent-citizens/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/04/strengthening-and-unleashing-americas-law-enforcement-to-pursue-criminals-and-protect-innocent-citizens/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Federal Immigration Enforcement and Community Protection Executive Order]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order outlines the federal government's authority over immigration and its commitment to protecting national security and communities from criminal activities associated with unauthorized immigration. The order establishes policies aimed at enforcing immigration laws and enhancing cooperation between federal, state, and local law enforcement agencies to ensure public safety. It reflects the administration's focus on the supremacy of federal laws regarding immigration and emphasizes the need for effective measures to address issues related to criminal activity by certain non-citizens. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/04/protecting-american-communities-from-criminal-aliens/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/04/protecting-american-communities-from-criminal-aliens/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>