<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:50:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Marking the 90th Anniversary of the Social Security Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation commemorates the 90th anniversary of the Social Security Act, originally signed into law by President Franklin D. Roosevelt on August 14, 1935. The proclamation describes the Act as establishing social insurance programs intended to provide financial security for the elderly and to support American workers, and it notes the Act's enduring role in promoting economic security. It affirms the continued commitment of the federal government to these programs and their administration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/90th-anniversary-of-the-social-security-act/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/90th-anniversary-of-the-social-security-act/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Revoking Executive Order 14036 (Promoting Competition in the American Economy)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential order revokes Executive Order 14036, titled Promoting Competition in the American Economy, which was issued on July 9, 2021. Section 1 of the order declares the revocation of EO 14036. Section 2 sets forth general provisions, including a clause beginning 'Nothing in this order shall be construed...', the remainder of which is not shown in the provided text. The document is presented as a presidential action issued under the authority of the Constitution and laws of the United States and is published on the White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/revocation-of-executive-order-on-competition/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/revocation-of-executive-order-on-competition/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Promote Competition in the Commercial Space Industry]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order sets forth the policy objective of increasing competition in the United States commercial space sector. It references historical milestones in space exploration, including the 1969 Moon landing, and notes ongoing activity by space companies worldwide. The document outlines the purpose of the order, aims to identify and address barriers to entry, streamline interagency processes, coordinate actions across government, and encourage participation by multiple entities in commercial space activities while prioritizing safety and national interests. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/enabling-competition-in-the-commercial-space-industry/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/enabling-competition-in-the-commercial-space-industry/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Strengthen Domestic Pharmaceutical Production and Replenish the Strategic Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients Reserve]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order uses presidential authority to enhance the resilience of the United States pharmaceutical supply chain. It directs federal agencies to pursue actions that increase domestic production capacity for essential pharmaceutical products and to fill the Strategic Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients Reserve, with the aim of improving health security and reducing supply vulnerabilities. The order builds on prior administrative efforts to restore domestic production capacity and provides for interagency coordination to implement steps necessary to secure a reliable supply of active pharmaceutical ingredients. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/ensuring-american-pharmaceutical-supply-chain-resilience-by-filling-the-strategic-active-pharmaceutical-ingredients-reserve/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/ensuring-american-pharmaceutical-supply-chain-resilience-by-filling-the-strategic-active-pharmaceutical-ingredients-reserve/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action to Adjust Reciprocal Tariff Rates with the People's Republic of China in Light of Ongoing Discussions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action, issued under the authority of the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, modifies reciprocal tariff rates applicable to goods imported from the People's Republic of China. The adjustments are intended to reflect ongoing bilateral discussions and negotiations with China and to implement current U.S. trade policy objectives. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/further-modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-to-reflect-ongoing-discussions-with-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/further-modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-to-reflect-ongoing-discussions-with-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum to the Secretary of Defense on Restoring Law and Order in the District of Columbia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum directs the Secretary of Defense to undertake measures to restore public safety and order in the District of Columbia. It emphasizes the President's role as Commander in Chief of the District of Columbia National Guard and calls for coordination with federal and local authorities to address criminal activity and protect law-abiding residents and visitors. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/restoring-law-and-order-in-the-district-of-columbia/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/restoring-law-and-order-in-the-district-of-columbia/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Declaration of a Crime Emergency in the District of Columbia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The action declares a crime emergency in the District of Columbia, issued by the President under constitutional authority and specific federal statutes, including Section 740 of the District of Columbia Self-Government and Governmental Reorganization Act (as amended), the Home Rule Act, and 3 U.S.C. 301. The declaration identifies the existence of a crime emergency and authorizes federal actions and coordination to support public safety efforts in the District of Columbia. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/declaring-a-crime-emergency-in-the-district-of-columbia/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/declaring-a-crime-emergency-in-the-district-of-columbia/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Expand Access to Alternative Asset Investments for 401(k) Plan Participants]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs federal agencies to evaluate the current regulatory framework governing retirement plan investments with the aim of expanding access to alternative asset investments for 401(k) plan participants. It notes that wealthier individuals and government workers in public pension plans often have access to a broader range of alternative assets and seeks to broaden similar opportunities for 401(k) investors. The order requires agency reviews, identification of barriers, and recommendations for actions to increase permissible investment options while preserving fiduciary duties, participant protections, and retirement security. It emphasizes prudent investment management, transparency, and oversight to ensure the sound handling of retirement assets. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/democratizing-access-to-alternative-assets-for-401k-investors/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/democratizing-access-to-alternative-assets-for-401k-investors/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Promote Fair Access to Banking Services for Americans]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive order directing federal agencies to address discriminatory practices by financial institutions that restrict access to banking and financial services for law-abiding individuals and businesses based on political beliefs, religious beliefs, or lawful business activities. The order states the objective of guaranteeing fair access to banking for all Americans and tasks relevant agencies with identifying barriers, enforcing applicable nondiscrimination and fair-lending laws, and promoting inclusive banking practices. It calls for coordination among regulators, development of compliance measures, and regular reporting on actions taken to improve access to financial services and reduce barriers to banking. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/guaranteeing-fair-banking-for-all-americans/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/guaranteeing-fair-banking-for-all-americans/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum Directing the Secretary of Education to Promote Transparency in Higher Education Admissions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential memorandum, issued by the President under constitutional and statutory authority, directs the Secretary of Education to take actions aimed at promoting transparency in higher education admissions. The document includes a background section referencing the Supreme Court's definitive ruling on the consideration of race in admissions and instructs the Department of Education to address transparency in the policies and practices governing admissions at higher education institutions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/ensuring-transparency-in-higher-education-admissions/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/08/ensuring-transparency-in-higher-education-admissions/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>