<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Michael McDonald to serve as Chairperson of the National Endowment for the Humanities for a four-year term, succeeding Shelly C. Lowe]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Michael McDonald, of the District of Columbia, has been nominated to serve as chairperson of the National Endowment for the Humanities for a four-year term, succeeding Shelly C. Lowe. The nomination is included in the White House release titled Nominations Sent to the Senate, which presents nominations sent to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-2f25/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-2f25/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Addressing Threats to the United States by the Government of Cuba]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President exercises authority under the Constitution, the International Emergency Economic Powers Act (IEEPA), the National Emergencies Act (NEA), and section 301 of title 3, United States Code, to determine and order measures intended to address threats posed by the Government of Cuba. The excerpt indicates that Section 1 contains the initial actions to be taken and that the document outlines the scope and implementation of these measures. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-cuba/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-cuba/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Addiction through the Great American Recovery Initiative]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order states the President's policy to address substance use disorder, also known as addiction, as a national crisis that affects families and communities. It begins with Section 1, Purpose and Policy, and introduces the framework for the Great American Recovery Initiative. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-addiction-through-the-great-american-recovery-initiative/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-addiction-through-the-great-american-recovery-initiative/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Declaring the Year of Celebration and Rededication, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating the calendar year 2026 as the Year of Celebration and Rededication to commemorate the 250th anniversary of United States independence. The document notes the founding date of July 4, 1776 and announces a year-long observance beginning January 1, 2026, describing the milestone in terms of national freedom and independence. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/year-of-celebration-and-rededication-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/year-of-celebration-and-rededication-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Rebuilding in Los Angeles After Wildfire Disasters: Assessment of State and Local Coordination]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order outlines the President's authority to address rebuilding efforts in Los Angeles following major wildfire disasters. It references an event from one year prior in which the California state government and the city and county governments of Los Angeles failed to contain wildfires that ravaged the area, resulting in roughly 40,000 acres of property damage. The document establishes the purpose of the order as evaluating and supporting the rebuilding process, coordinating federal assistance, and improving accountability for state and local actions related to wildfire response and recovery. It specifies that the order provides the framework for federal involvement in disaster response and rebuilding and sets the stage for potential actions, reporting requirements, and implementation steps to address such failures in the future. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on the Continuation of the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order continues the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council, which was established by a prior executive action. It states that the President's authority to issue the order stems from the Constitution and applicable laws, and it specifies that the council operates under the Federal Advisory Committee Act, codified at 5 U.S.C. chapter 10. The order preserves the council's mandate to provide independent advice to the President and the Administrator of the Federal Emergency Management Agency on matters concerning FEMA programs, policies, and activities. It requires the council to function in accordance with FACA and to report and coordinate as described in the order, thereby maintaining the council's existence for the duration of the directive or until superseded by future action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>