<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:00:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Executive Order Modifying Duties on Imports to Address Threats Posed by the Government of the Russian Federation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action, issued under the President's authority from the Constitution and multiple statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act, modifies duties (tariffs) applicable to imports in response to threats identified by the Government of the Russian Federation. The order cites the Trade Act of 1974 as amended as part of the authority and directs the relevant agencies to implement the changes, including applicable effective dates and regulations necessary to enforce the modified duties, thereby adjusting the U.S. tariff framework in relation to concerns about the Russian government. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/modifying-duties-to-address-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-the-russian-federation-04b2/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/modifying-duties-to-address-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-the-russian-federation-04b2/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing a Strategy for United States Arms Transfers Emphasizing American-Made Military Equipment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action directs the development and implementation of United States policy governing the transfer of defense articles and services. It emphasizes American-made military equipment as a central asset in national defense export capabilities and describes the objective of leveraging the United States’ comparative advantage in international defense markets. The order outlines the overarching aim to align arms-transfer activities with United States national security and foreign policy priorities and to establish a framework for pursuing these priorities across the executive branch. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/establishing-an-america-first-arms-transfer-strategy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/establishing-an-america-first-arms-transfer-strategy/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Protecting the National Security and Welfare of the United States and Its Citizens from Criminal Actors and Public Safety Threats]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes the policy of the United States to safeguard national security and the welfare of the American people from criminal actors and other public safety threats. It asserts authority under the Constitution and applicable federal law, including 6 U.S.C. 122(a)(2), and directs federal agencies to coordinate actions, assess risks, share information, and implement measures to prevent, mitigate, and respond to criminal activity and related public safety threats. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/protecting-the-national-security-and-welfare-of-the-united-states-and-its-citizens-from-criminal-actors-and-other-public-safety-threats/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/protecting-the-national-security-and-welfare-of-the-united-states-and-its-citizens-from-criminal-actors-and-other-public-safety-threats/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Policy Update on Atlantic Commercial Fishing and Reference to Northeast Canyons and Seamounts Marine National Monument]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Describes a White House policy update regarding commercial fishing in the Atlantic Ocean. The post references President Obama’s 2016 Proclamation 9496 designating the Northeast Canyons and Seamounts Marine National Monument and designating approximately 4,913 square miles of Atlantic waters and submerged lands at the continental shelf boundary as part of the national monument under the Antiquities Act. The summary outlines considerations for regulating or enabling commercial fishing operations in the Atlantic and describes related administrative actions and authorities for managing Atlantic fisheries, emphasizing a balance between conservation objectives and fishing activities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/unleashing-american-commercial-fishing-in-the-atlantic/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/unleashing-american-commercial-fishing-in-the-atlantic/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Ensuring Availability and Affordability of Beef for American Consumers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation acknowledges the historical role of cattle ranchers in the United States, notes that beef remains a staple in the American diet, and states the President’s objective to ensure affordable access to beef for American consumers. It recognizes stakeholders in the beef supply chain and outlines the goal of supporting beef production and distribution in a manner that maintains affordability. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/ensuring-affordable-beef-for-the-american-consumer/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/ensuring-affordable-beef-for-the-american-consumer/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Michael McDonald to be Chairperson of the National Endowment for the Humanities for a four-year term, succeeding Shelly C. Lowe]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Michael McDonald, of the District of Columbia, has been nominated to serve as Chairperson of the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) for a four-year term, succeeding Shelly C. Lowe. The nomination has been sent to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-2f25/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-2f25/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>