<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:00:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential permit for the expansion and operation of a border crossing at the Camino Real International Bridge in Eagle Pass, Texas]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President of the United States has authorized the City of Eagle Pass, Texas, to expand, maintain, and operate a vehicular and pedestrian border crossing at the Camino Real International Bridge. This permit is granted under specific conditions outlined by the authorities and allows the city to continue managing cross-border transportation facilities at this port of entry. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing the General Terms of the United States of America-United Kingdom Economic Prosperity Deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action is taken to implement the general terms of the economic agreement between the United States of America and the United Kingdom, establishing frameworks for economic cooperation and prosperity. The authority to do so is based on the President's constitutional powers and statutory authorities, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and the Trade Expansion Act of 1962 section 232. The initiative aims to promote economic collaboration and address relevant issues as outlined in the agreement. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Permit Authorization for the Expansion and Operation of a Vehicular Border Crossing at the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge Land Port of Entry]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President of the United States grants permission to the City of Laredo, Texas, to expand, maintain, and operate a vehicular crossing at the Laredo-Colombia Solidarity International Bridge Land Port of Entry, subject to specified conditions. This permit allows continued and expanded use of the international border infrastructure for vehicular traffic. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-laredo-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-border-crossing-at-the-laredo-colombia-solidarity-international-bridge-land-port/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>