<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:00:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Permit for the Expansion and Operation of a Border Crossing at the Camino Real International Bridge in Eagle Pass, Texas]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President of the United States granted permission to the City of Eagle Pass, Texas, to expand and continue to operate a vehicular and pedestrian border crossing at the Camino Real International Bridge. This permit is subject to specified conditions and authorizes ongoing maintenance and operation of the border crossing infrastructure at this land port of entry. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/presidential-permit-authorizing-the-city-of-eagle-pass-texas-to-expand-and-continue-to-maintain-and-operate-a-vehicular-and-pedestrian-border-crossing-at-the-camino-real-international-bridge-land-po/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing the Terms of the United States-United Kingdom Economic Prosperity Deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action establishes procedures for implementing the general terms of an economic agreement between the United States and the United Kingdom. It authorizes the application of relevant laws, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and the Trade Expansion Act, to facilitate cooperation and economic initiatives outlined in the deal. The order aims to advance economic relations and prosperity between the two nations through specified measures and administrative processes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/implementing-the-general-terms-of-the-united-states-of-america-united-kingdom-economic-prosperity-deal/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>