<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 12:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Modifying Tariff Scope for the Government of Brazil]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President, acting under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, issues an executive action that modifies the scope of tariffs applicable to the Government of Brazil. The action cites the legal basis for the modification and outlines the scope and implementation of the tariff changes as they pertain to the Government of Brazil. The announcement is published on the White House's presidential actions platform and references the relevant statutes and regulatory framework used to justify the action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modifying the Scope of the Reciprocal Tariff with Respect to Certain Agricultural Products]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action, issued under the authority vested in the President by the Constitution and U.S. law, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, modifies the scope of the reciprocal tariff with respect to certain agricultural products. The action defines which agricultural products are subject to the reciprocal tariff framework within those authorities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-the-reciprocal-tariff-with-respect-to-certain-agricultural-products/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Veterans Day, 2025 by the President of the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation, issued by the President of the United States for Veterans Day 2025, acknowledges the courage, honor, and dedicated service of United States veterans, reflects on how their sacrifices have supported the nation’s freedoms and way of life, and calls on the American people to observe Veterans Day with appropriate remembrance and ceremonies. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Commemorating the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Marine Corps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation designates a national observance recognizing the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Marine Corps. It describes the Marine Corps’ history and its role in serving the nation, and it invites federal, state, and local governments, as well as the public, to observe the milestone through appropriate ceremonies, educational activities, and other commemorations that honor the service and legacy of Marines. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jared Isaacman to be Administrator of NASA]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced the nomination of Jared Isaacman, a resident of Pennsylvania, to serve as Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration. The nomination would succeed Bill Nelson, who has resigned from the post. The nomination has been sent to the Senate for consideration and confirmation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>