<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Thanksgiving Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating Thanksgiving Day for 2025 and situates the observance within the historical tradition that began with President George Washington in 1789, which established the first National Day of Thanksgiving and urged nations to acknowledge Providence, obey His will, and express gratitude for blessings. The proclamation invites Americans to observe the day with reflection and gratitude for the nation’s blessings and for those who serve the country, and it directs appropriate observances by government and the public. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Declaring Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Coke Oven Processing Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation notes the vital role of steel in the United States economy and daily life and announces regulatory relief for certain stationary sources intended to promote the security and reliability of American coke oven processing used in steel production. The document describes the scope of the relief, the agencies involved, and the objectives of easing regulatory requirements to support coke oven operations, while maintaining appropriate regulatory oversight. It directs relevant federal agencies to implement the relief and to monitor its effects and determine if further adjustments are necessary. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-coke-oven-processing-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-coke-oven-processing-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Federal Positions Including ATF Director, EEOC General Counsel, and CFPB Director]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for multiple federal positions, including Robert Cekada of Florida as Director of the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms, and Explosives; Carter Crow of Texas as General Counsel of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission for a four-year term; Stuart Levenbach of Maryland as Director of the Bureau of Consumer Financial Protection for a five-year term; and David Clay Fowlkes, among other nominees, for additional positions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-d2ae/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-d2ae/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Adoption Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating November 2025 as National Adoption Month. The proclamation highlights the importance of secure and nurturing homes for children, describes adoption as a means to provide stability and belonging, and acknowledges the contributions of adoptive families and parents during the observance. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/national-adoption-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/national-adoption-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Supporting Safe Families and Foster Care]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's constitutional authority, establishes the policy direction of the administration regarding family support and the foster care system. The document emphasizes promoting safe and loving homes for children and addresses the role of foster care in responding to crises that disrupt family arrangements. Section 1, titled Purpose and Policy, outlines the administration's objectives to support families and to address conditions affecting family stability, including foster care, through coordination and guidance across relevant federal actions. The order is intended to guide federal policy and interagency cooperation to uphold these aims for American children and families. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/fostering-the-future-for-american-children-and-families/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/fostering-the-future-for-american-children-and-families/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>