<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Concerning the Acquisition of Certain Emcore Corporation Assets by Hiefo Corporation under the Defense Production Act]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive order issued by the President under the Defense Production Act of 1950, as amended, specifically Section 721, regarding the acquisition of certain Emcore Corporation assets by Hiefo Corporation. The document opens with findings indicating the President has credible evidence related to the matter and establishes the authority to take actions under Section 721, outlining the steps to be taken in compliance with the Defense Production Act. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/regarding-the-acquisition-of-certain-assets-of-emcore-corporation-by-hiefo-corporation/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum on Coordinating United States 6G Technology Development]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This National Security Presidential Memorandum directs multiple federal departments and agencies to coordinate and accelerate United States efforts in the research, development, and deployment of sixth-generation wireless technology (6G). It assigns responsibilities to key agencies including the Department of State, the Department of Defense, the Department of Commerce, the Department of Transportation, the Department of Energy, the Department of Homeland Security, the Office of Management and Budget, the Office of the Director of National Intelligence, the Federal Communications Commission, and the White House policy offices. The memorandum aims to enhance U.S. leadership in 6G, address national security considerations, and promote secure and resilient supply chains, standards development, and collaboration with industry and international partners as part of a coordinated national strategy. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-security-presidential-memorandum-nspm-8-0bda/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>