<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Threats to the United States by the Government of Cuba]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action, issued under the authority of the Constitution and federal statutes including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act, declares a national emergency in response to threats posed by the Government of Cuba and establishes measures to counter those threats. The order authorizes sanctions and restrictions on certain transactions and property, directs federal agencies to implement and enforce the measures, and sets forth the scope, reporting requirements, and duration of the emergency powers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-cuba/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-cuba/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Addiction through the Great American Recovery Initiative]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order sets forth the president's policy to address substance use disorder as a national crisis and describes a framework for coordinating federal actions under the Great American Recovery Initiative. It notes that addiction affects families in every community and outlines the purposes of the order in Section 1 (Purpose and Policy), including interagency coordination, programmatic actions, and resource alignment intended to support prevention, treatment, and recovery efforts nationwide. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-addiction-through-the-great-american-recovery-initiative/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-addiction-through-the-great-american-recovery-initiative/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Declaring 2026 as the Year of Celebration and Rededication to Commemorate the 250th Anniversary of U.S. Independence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation designates the year 2026 as the Year of Celebration and Rededication to commemorate the 250th anniversary of the United States' founding. Beginning January 1, 2026, the United States is to observe national observances and encourage educational, cultural, and community activities that reflect on the nation's history, founding principles, and commitment to democracy. It calls on federal agencies, states, localities, organizations, and citizens to participate in programs and partnerships that promote awareness of the anniversary through public commemorations, historical education, and civic engagement. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/year-of-celebration-and-rededication-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/year-of-celebration-and-rededication-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Rebuilding Efforts in Los Angeles After Wildfire Disasters]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's authority, states its purpose to address rebuilding efforts in Los Angeles following wildfire disasters. It notes that one year earlier, state and local governments in California—the state and the City and County of Los Angeles—failed to contain wildfires that ravaged the area, resulting in the destruction of nearly 40,000 acres of homes and businesses. The document sets forth the objective of addressing post-disaster rebuilding in the affected region and references the need to address these failures within the scope of federal action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuance of the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive action continues the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council, an advisory body established by an executive action and operating under the Federal Advisory Committee Act. The order formalizes the continuation of the Council's existence and its functions, and it reiterates that the Council will operate in accordance with applicable law to provide advisory input on matters related to the Federal Emergency Management Agency. Section 1 confirms that the Council, created by a prior executive action, shall remain in effect and continue performing its duties as authorized. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Martin Luther King Jr. Federal Holiday for 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues a proclamation designating the Martin Luther King Jr. Federal Holiday for 2026, honoring Reverend Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. for his commitment to justice and equality, and invoking the Declaration of Independence as a basis for renewing the nation's pledge to the American promise. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/martin-luther-king-jr-federal-holiday-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/martin-luther-king-jr-federal-holiday-2026/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>