<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Addressing Security Risks from Price Fixing and Anti-Competitive Behavior in the Food Supply Chain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order identifies the importance of a secure and affordable food supply for national and economic security. It notes concerns about price fixing and anti-competitive behavior, including actions by foreign-controlled corporations, and directs federal agencies to coordinate actions to assess, monitor, and mitigate these risks within the food supply chain to safeguard stability and consumer access to affordable food. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/addressing-security-risks-from-price-fixing-and-anti-competitive-behavior-in-the-food-supply-chain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/addressing-security-risks-from-price-fixing-and-anti-competitive-behavior-in-the-food-supply-chain/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Honoring the Memory of Specialist Sarah Beckstrom, West Virginia Army National Guard]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation honors the memory of Specialist Sarah Beckstrom of the West Virginia Army National Guard and directs that the flag of the United States be flown at half-staff as a mark of respect. The document explains the authority for the action and indicates that the half-staff requirement applies to federal properties and U.S. military installations for the period specified in the proclamation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/honoring-the-memory-of-specialist-sarah-beckstrom-west-virginia-army-national-guard/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/honoring-the-memory-of-specialist-sarah-beckstrom-west-virginia-army-national-guard/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[America 250: Presidential Message on the Anniversary of the Monroe Doctrine]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A White House presidential message commemorating the Monroe Doctrine on its anniversary, recounting its historical rationale and significance and stating that the current administration reaffirms the United States' commitment to defending the homeland, national interests, and citizens. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/america-250-presidential-message-on-the-anniversary-of-the-monroe-doctrine/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/america-250-presidential-message-on-the-anniversary-of-the-monroe-doctrine/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate, including James Bishop, of North Carolina, to be United States Attorney for the Middle District of North Carolina for a four-year term; Megan Blair Benton, of Missouri, to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri; and Christopher Michael De Bono, of the District of Columbia, to be an Associate Judge (specific court not specified in the excerpt). Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Message Commemorating Mark Twain’s 190th Birthday as Part of the America 250 Initiative]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This White House post, issued under the America 250 initiative, presents a presidential message commemorating the 190th birthday of Mark Twain. It notes Twain as a significant American writer and describes his impact on American literature and culture through storytelling, humor, and imagination. The message places Twain’s legacy within the nation’s broader effort to recognize and celebrate American literary history, reflecting on his contributions and the relevance of his work to the country's cultural heritage. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/america-250-presidential-message-on-mark-twains-190th-birthday/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/america-250-presidential-message-on-mark-twains-190th-birthday/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>