<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:00:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Appointment of Alex Meyer as Deputy Assistant to the President and Director of the White House Office of Intergovernmental Affairs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Alex Meyer has been appointed as the Deputy Assistant to the President and will serve as the Director of the White House Office of Intergovernmental Affairs. In his previous role, Meyer worked as the Deputy Political Director for the Trump-Vance 2024 Campaign, where he managed electoral operations in several battleground states, including Georgia, North Carolina, and Pennsylvania. This appointment is part of the administration's strategy to enhance intergovernmental relations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-appointments-to-the-white-house-office-of-intergovernmental-affairs/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-trump-announces-appointments-to-the-white-house-office-of-intergovernmental-affairs/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Federal Support for Migration Enforcement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order outlines the intention of the President to enforce existing federal laws related to immigration and public assistance. It emphasizes the legal restrictions that prevent individuals residing in the country unlawfully from accessing certain federal benefits, specifically referencing the Personal Responsibility and Work Opportunity Reconciliation Act of 1996. The order indicates a commitment to ensure that taxpayer-funded resources are not allocated to support unauthorized migration and seeks to align federal policy with these legal guidelines. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/ending-taxpayer-subsidization-of-open-borders/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/ending-taxpayer-subsidization-of-open-borders/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guidance on Transparency in Government Spending]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum outlines directives for the heads of executive departments and agencies regarding the importance of increasing transparency in government spending. It addresses concerns about expenditure on programs, contracts, and grants that may not align with the interests of American taxpayers. The memorandum emphasizes the need for oversight and accountability in government financial practices, particularly concerning funding for projects both domestically and internationally that may not serve the public good. It calls for a review of existing spending and encourages a focus on efficiency and responsibility in future allocations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/radical-transparency-about-wasteful-spending/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/radical-transparency-about-wasteful-spending/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation for George Washington's Birthday, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation issued by the President of the United States recognizes and commemorates the birthday of George Washington, the first President of the United States. It highlights his contributions to the nation and the ideals he represents. The proclamation serves to honor Washington's legacy and acknowledges his role as a foundational figure in American history. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-george-washingtons-birthday-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/president-george-washingtons-birthday-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>