<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates December 7, 2025 as National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day to commemorate the attack on Pearl Harbor on December 7, 1941. The proclamation notes the historical significance of the events and encourages observances, ceremonies, and educational activities to reflect on the impact of the attack and remember those who defended the United States. The designation underscores the importance of reflecting on this event in United States history. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum to Align United States Core Childhood Vaccine Recommendations with Best Practices from Peer Developed Countries]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A memorandum directing the Secretary of Health and Human Services and the Director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to align the United States' core childhood vaccine recommendations with best practices observed in peer developed countries. The action follows the January 2025 expansion of U.S. immunization to cover 18 diseases for all children, including COVID-19, and seeks to harmonize U.S. immunization guidelines with international standards. The memorandum tasks national health agencies to evaluate current schedules, compare with peer country practices, identify opportunities to streamline or adjust recommendations, ensure safety and efficacy considerations are addressed, and engage with stakeholders as part of the alignment process, including establishing timelines for reporting progress and implementing changes as appropriate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates December 7, 2025, as National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day. The proclamation references the December 7, 1941 attack on Pearl Harbor and its impact on the Nation, and directs that the day be observed with appropriate ceremonies and educational activities across the United States to honor those who served and those affected during World War II, and to reflect on the lessons of that period. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for United States Attorney for the Middle District of North Carolina, United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri, and an Associate Judge position]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced three nominations to be forwarded to the Senate: James Bishop, of North Carolina, to serve as United States Attorney for the Middle District of North Carolina for a four-year term; Megan Blair Benton, of Missouri, to serve as United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri; and Christopher Michael De Bono, of the District of Columbia, to serve as an Associate Judge of a federal court (court unspecified in the provided excerpt). Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-a9f3/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: Thanksgiving Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President designating Thanksgiving Day, 2025. It references the historical origin of the national day of thanksgiving, noting that in 1789 President George Washington established the first such day and described a duty to acknowledge the providence of Almighty God, obey His will, and be grateful for blessings. The proclamation designates Thanksgiving Day, 2025, and calls upon federal, state, and local governments, as well as individuals and communities, to observe the day with acts of gratitude and reflection on the nation's history and blessings. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/thanksgiving-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>