<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:00:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jared Isaacman to be Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced the nomination of Jared Isaacman, a resident of Pennsylvania, to serve as Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, to succeed Bill Nelson who resigned. The nomination has been sent to the United States Senate for consideration, indicating the formal step of submitting the nomination to the Senate for confirmation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modifying Reciprocal Tariff Rates Consistent with the U.S.-China Economic and Trade Arrangement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Presidential action under authorities including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974 to modify reciprocal tariff rates between the United States and the People's Republic of China. The action implements or adjusts tariffs as part of the Economic and Trade Arrangement between the two nations, aligning tariff rates with the agreed terms and applicable law. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Modifying Import Duties to Address the Synthetic Opioid Supply Chain in the People's Republic of China]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority granted by the Constitution and federal law, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, the President modifies import duties applicable to goods from the People's Republic of China. The action is intended to address the synthetic opioid supply chain and outlines the scope and application of the duty modifications in accordance with these authorities. The measure is documented as a presidential action posted on the White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination Sent to Senate for U.S. District Judges in Louisiana and a U.S. Marshal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that nominations have been sent to the Senate for three federal positions: William J. Crain, of Louisiana, to be United States District Judge for the Eastern District of Louisiana, to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Eldon E. Fallon; Alexander C. Van Hook, of Louisiana, to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Louisiana, to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Elizabeth Erny Foote; and Brian Barber, of Louisiana, to be United States Marshal. The notice, titled Nomination Sent to the Senate, appeared on The White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Energy Dominance Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designating National Energy Dominance Month for 2025. It notes the United States' long-standing reliance on energy resources such as oil, coal, minerals, and natural gas, and references geographic regions from the Appalachian Mountains to the Great Plains. The proclamation emphasizes recognizing and highlighting the nation's energy resources as part of national policy and national security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-energy-dominance-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-energy-dominance-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Declaring National Cybersecurity Awareness Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates October 2025 as National Cybersecurity Awareness Month. It notes that advances in cybersecurity have led to new threats to national defense and public safety, and it reaffirms the administration's commitment to strengthening the nation's cybersecurity to improve the lives of Americans, defend national sovereignty, and uphold the rights of all citizens. The proclamation calls for heightened public awareness, education, and coordinated action across federal, state, and local governments, the private sector, and the public to enhance cybersecurity resilience, protect critical infrastructure, and promote responsible digital practices while safeguarding privacy and civil rights. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-cybersecurity-awareness-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-cybersecurity-awareness-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>