<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 11:00:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Automobiles and Automobile Parts]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation addresses the findings from a report submitted by the Secretary of Commerce regarding the impact of imports of passenger vehicles and light trucks on the national security of the United States. The Secretary's investigation focuses on various categories of automobiles, including sedans, sport utility vehicles, and light trucks. The proclamation outlines measures intended to adjust the importation of these vehicles and associated parts to safeguard national interests. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/adjusting-imports-of-automobiles-and-autombile-parts-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/adjusting-imports-of-automobiles-and-autombile-parts-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Grant of Clemency for Devon Archer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This document is an official announcement from President Donald J. Trump regarding the granting of a full and unconditional pardon to an individual named Devon Archer. The pardon is issued under the authority of Article II, Section 2, Clause 1 of the U.S. Constitution. The announcement signifies the president's legal power to grant clemency for offenses committed by individuals, although specific details about the offenses are not disclosed in this statement. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/executive-grant-of-clemency-for-devon-archer/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/executive-grant-of-clemency-for-devon-archer/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imposition of Tariffs on Imported Venezuelan Oil]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes tariffs on countries that import oil from Venezuela. The action is taken under the authority provided by the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and relevant sections of the U.S. Code. The order aims to address foreign relations and economic conditions related to Venezuelan oil imports. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/imposing-tariffs-on-countries-importing-venezuelan-oil/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/imposing-tariffs-on-countries-importing-venezuelan-oil/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation for Greek Independence Day: A National Celebration of Greek and American Democracy, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation commemorates the 204th anniversary of Greek Independence Day, recognizing the efforts of Greek revolutionaries in their struggle for independence from the Ottoman Empire which resulted in the establishment of a sovereign Greek state. The proclamation emphasizes the significance of this day in celebrating both Greek and American democratic values. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/greek-independence-day-a-national-day-of-celebration-of-greek-and-american-democracy-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/greek-independence-day-a-national-day-of-celebration-of-greek-and-american-democracy-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>