<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for U.S. Attorney for the District of Nevada and Assistant Secretaries]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for: George Kelesis of Nevada to be United States Attorney for the District of Nevada for a four-year term, succeeding Jason M. Frierson; Catherine Dillon of Maryland to be Assistant Secretary of State for Educational and Cultural Affairs, succeeding Lee Satterfield; William Hague of Washington to be Assistant Secretary of the Interior. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-b65f/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing United States National Defense Through a Clean Coal Power Generation Fleet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House post discusses ensuring the electric grid remains resilient and reliable to support military installations, operations, and defense-industrial production. It describes the grid as foundational to national defense and economic stability and notes concerns about potential prolonged disruptions from energy supply variability. The document outlines a strategy to strengthen energy security by deploying a fleet of clean coal power generation facilities, intended to provide reliable, low-emission electricity as part of a broader effort to reduce dependence on intermittent energy sources and to maintain continuous power for critical defense functions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/strengthening-united-states-national-defense-with-americas-beautiful-clean-coal-power-generation-fleet/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Addressing Threats to the United States by the Government of Iran]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action asserts authority under the Constitution and multiple federal statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and provisions of the Trade Act of 1974 (including section 604 and related authorities), to address threats posed by the Government of Iran. The action indicates the use of emergency powers and other measures authorized to respond to identified risks to U.S. national security, and it is published as a presidential action dated February 2026 on the White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/02/addressing-threats-to-the-united-states-by-the-government-of-iran/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>