<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 12:00:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: Veterans Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation designates Veterans Day, 2025, to honor United States military veterans. It acknowledges the courage, honor, and dedicated service of veterans, describes their sacrifices in defending freedom and the American way of life, and expresses national gratitude while calling for appropriate ceremonies and remembrance on Veterans Day. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/veterans-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on the 250th Anniversary of the Founding of the United States Marine Corps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation commemorates the 250th anniversary of the founding of the United States Marine Corps, highlighting its historical role in American defense and its enduring commitments to courage, discipline, and unity. It references the Corps' origins in 1775 and its continued service through subsequent generations, and it encourages appropriate national observances and recognition of Marines, their families, and civilian personnel who support the Corps. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/250th-anniversary-of-the-founding-of-the-united-states-marine-corps/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination Sent to Senate for Jared Isaacman to Be Administrator of NASA]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that Jared Isaacman, a resident of Pennsylvania, has been nominated to serve as Administrator of the National Aeronautics and Space Administration, succeeding Bill Nelson who has resigned. The nomination has been sent to the Senate for confirmation and Senate consideration. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-7385/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modifying Reciprocal Tariff Rates Under the US–China Economic and Trade Arrangement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action cites the authority of the Constitution and several statutes, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, to modify reciprocal tariff rates. The modification is described as being consistent with the economic and trade arrangement between the United States and the People's Republic of China. The action reflects the executive branch's use of applicable legal authorities to adjust tariff levels in support of the stated trade framework between the two countries. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-reciprocal-tariff-rates-consistent-with-the-economic-and-trade-arrangement-between-the-united-states-and-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modifying Duties Addressing the Synthetic Opioid Supply Chain in the People's Republic of China]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action exercises authorities under the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, as amended, to modify U.S. import duties in order to address the synthetic opioid supply chain associated with the People's Republic of China. The action involves adjusting tariff measures applicable to goods from China to influence the importation of items related to the synthetic opioid supply chain. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Louisiana Federal Judicial Positions and a U.S. Marshal Appointment]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced that nominations have been sent to the Senate for three federal positions in Louisiana: William J. Crain, of Louisiana, to be United States District Judge for the Eastern District of Louisiana, to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Eldon E. Fallon; Alexander C. Van Hook, of Louisiana, to be United States District Judge for the Western District of Louisiana, to fill the vacancy created by the retirement of Elizabeth Erny Foote; and Brian Barber, of Louisiana, to be United States Marshal for the District of Louisiana. The announcements identify retirements as the basis for the vacancies in the judicial positions and indicate a nomination process proceeding to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate-f090/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>