<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:00:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoration of the Public Service Loan Forgiveness Program]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order aims to restore and enhance the Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) Program, which was established by Congress in 2007. The PSLF Program is designed to incentivize individuals to pursue careers in public service by offering student loan forgiveness after a specified period of qualifying employment. The order outlines measures to ensure better accessibility and administration of the program, reinforcing the commitment to support public service professionals and improve the effectiveness of loan forgiveness for eligible borrowers. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/restoring-public-service-loan-forgiveness/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/restoring-public-service-loan-forgiveness/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of the White House Task Force for the FIFA World Cup 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes a task force under the authority of the President of the United States to oversee and coordinate preparations for the FIFA World Cup 2026, which the United States will host. The task force is tasked with addressing logistics, security, infrastructure, and other necessary arrangements to ensure a successful event. The activities of the task force will focus on collaboration among federal, state, and local entities, as well as engagement with stakeholders in the sports and entertainment sectors. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/establishing-the-white-house-task-force-on-the-fifa-world-cup-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/establishing-the-white-house-task-force-on-the-fifa-world-cup-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Further Amendment to Duties on Synthetic Opioids from China]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order outlines modifications to duties aimed at regulating the synthetic opioid supply chain originating from the People's Republic of China. It is issued under the authority provided by the International Emergency Economic Powers Act and the National Emergencies Act, among other legal frameworks. The amendment seeks to address specific economic and health-related concerns linked to the proliferation of synthetic opioids. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/further-amendment-to-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/03/further-amendment-to-duties-addressing-the-synthetic-opioid-supply-chain-in-the-peoples-republic-of-china/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>