<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Coordinating Federal Efforts to Rebuild Los Angeles After Wildfire Disasters]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issues an executive order to coordinate federal agency actions in response to wildfires that devastated Los Angeles about one year earlier, noting that state and local governments were unable to contain the fires and that nearly 40,000 acres of homes and businesses were burned. The order outlines its purposes to facilitate rebuilding and recovery, clarify the roles of federal agencies, expedite assistance to affected communities, and strengthen resilience against future wildfires, in partnership with state and local authorities and other stakeholders. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/addressing-state-and-local-failures-to-rebuild-los-angeles-after-wildfire-disasters/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuance of the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An executive order issued by the President under the Federal Advisory Committee Act continues the Federal Emergency Management Agency Review Council, a federal advisory committee established by an earlier executive action. The order affirms the council's ongoing role in advising on matters related to Federal Emergency Management Agency programs and activities, specifies its legal basis, and directs its continued operation for a defined period to support federal emergency management planning, coordination, and policy recommendations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/continuance-of-the-federal-emergency-management-agency-review-council/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday, 2026]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issued a proclamation designating Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday for 2026, recognizing Reverend Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.'s leadership in advancing civil rights and his commitment to justice. The proclamation references the nation's founding ideals in the Declaration of Independence and affirms the nation's pledge to pursue equality and justice. It designates the federal holiday to be observed on the third Monday in January and encourages appropriate observances that reflect on King's legacy and the ongoing efforts toward justice. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/martin-luther-king-jr-federal-holiday-2026/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/martin-luther-king-jr-federal-holiday-2026/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate: Ademola Adewale-Sadik for U.S. Director of the African Development Bank and Charlton Allen for General Counsel of the Federal Labor Relations Authority, among others]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for several federal positions. Ademola Adewale-Sadik, of New York, was nominated to be United States Director of the African Development Bank for a five-year term, succeeding Oren E. Whyche-Shaw. Charlton Allen, of North Carolina, was nominated to be General Counsel of the Federal Labor Relations Authority for a five-year term, succeeding Julia Akins Clark. The listing also includes Matthew Anderson, with the remaining details not shown in the provided excerpt. This post is titled Nominations Sent to the Senate and appeared on The White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-078c/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-078c/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>