<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on Adjusting Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States Under Section 232]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation follows a Section 232 investigation conducted by the Secretary of Commerce, who on July 1, 2025 transmitted a report examining the effects of imports of timber, lumber, and their derivative products on United States national security. Based on that report, the President implements adjustments to the import of these wood products into the United States as authorized by Section 232. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Continuation of Selected Federal Advisory Committees Through September 30, 2027]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action, issued by the President, extends the duration of the federal advisory committees identified in Section 1 of the order. Under the authority granted by the Constitution and federal law, including the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. chapter 10), the order directs that the listed advisory committees remain in effect through September 30, 2027. The continuation is intended to maintain advisory services and requires adherence to applicable laws and procedures governing federal advisory committees. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum Directing Enforcement of Federal Death Penalty Laws in the District of Columbia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum, issued by the President and addressed to the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia, directs the enforcement of federal death penalty statutes within the District of Columbia. It states the objective to deter and punish the most serious offenses and designates the responsible officials to oversee the application of federal death penalty provisions in relevant cases, in accordance with applicable law. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day for 2025. The document recognizes the sacrifices of Gold Star Families—families of military service members who have died in the line of duty—and designates a day of remembrance to honor their contributions. It calls for appropriate observances and ceremonies across federal, state, and local communities to acknowledge the sacrifices of fallen service members and to support their surviving families. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-family%27s-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-family%27s-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Implementing the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act to Regulate Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications, Including TikTok]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive action directs federal agencies to implement and enforce the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (Public Law 118-50, Division H), which governs applications controlled by foreign adversaries. The order identifies the focus on TikTok or similar apps and assigns responsibilities to assess security risks, establish regulatory measures, and take steps to regulate, restrict, or oversee such applications as necessary to protect national security. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>