<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 11:00:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Marking the 160th Anniversary of the Establishment of the United States Secret Service in 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation commemorates the 160th anniversary of the founding of the United States Secret Service, established on April 14, 1865, by President Abraham Lincoln. The agency was created with the original purpose of investigating counterfeiting of U.S. currency and security documents. The proclamation reflects on the history and evolution of the agency since its inception. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/07/160th-anniversary-of-the-united-states-secret-service-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/07/160th-anniversary-of-the-united-states-secret-service-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Permit for South Bow (USA) LP to Operate and Maintain Pipeline Facilities at the U.S.-Canada Border in North Dakota]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President issued a permit to South Bow (USA) LP, a Delaware-registered limited partnership, authorizing the company to operate and maintain pipeline facilities located at Cavalier County, North Dakota, near the international boundary with Canada. The permit is granted subject to specified conditions outlined in the authorization. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/text-of-a-letter-from-the-president-to-the-speaker-of-the-house-of-representatives/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/06/text-of-a-letter-from-the-president-to-the-speaker-of-the-house-of-representatives/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>