<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:00:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: National Adoption Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims November 2025 as National Adoption Month to emphasize adoption's role in providing stable, nurturing homes for children and to reaffirm the commitment to child welfare. The proclamation notes that every child deserves a safe environment to learn and grow, acknowledges adoptive families and parents, and calls on federal agencies, organizations, and communities to support adoption efforts and reduce barriers to adoption and related services during National Adoption Month and beyond. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/national-adoption-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/national-adoption-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order on Supporting Safe Family Environments and Foster Care for American Children]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order states the administration's policy to empower parents to raise their children in safe and loving homes. It also addresses foster care in cases where such family arrangements are not possible, outlining the government's approach to child welfare and the foster care system in crisis situations. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/fostering-the-future-for-american-children-and-families/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/fostering-the-future-for-american-children-and-families/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Anti-Communism Week, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This document is a proclamation issued by the President of the United States designating a period as Anti-Communism Week in 2025. It notes the historical impact of regimes associated with communism across nations and generations. The proclamation calls for observances and reflections on the consequences of totalitarian ideologies, honors the memory of those affected, and reaffirms the nation's commitment to democratic principles and individual rights. It invites appropriate observances and reflection in line with national traditions. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/anti-communism-week-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for Assistant Attorney General, Director of the Bureau of Land Management, and Nuclear Regulatory Commission Member]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations sent to the Senate for three positions: Daniel E. Burrows of Colorado to be Assistant Attorney General (succeeding Aaron Reitz, who resigned); Stevan Pearce of New Mexico to be Director of the Bureau of Land Management (succeeding Tracy Stone-Manning, who resigned); and Douglas Weaver of Maryland to be a Member of the Nuclear Regulatory Commission for the remainder of the term expiring June 30. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-099e/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>