<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bill of Rights Day, 2025 Proclamation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Official presidential action proclaiming Bill of Rights Day in 2025. The proclamation commemorates the ratification of the Bill of Rights and places it in the context of the nation's founding, describing the conception of the United States in liberty, the endurance of freedom, and the nation's unity. It highlights the enduring principles of sovereignty, justice, and self-determination and emphasizes the importance of protecting and upholding the rights enshrined in the Bill of Rights for all citizens. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/bill-of-rights-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designating Fentanyl as a Weapon of Mass Destruction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order designates illicit fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction under the President's authorities. It states that illicit fentanyl is closer to a chemical weapon than a narcotic and references a very small threshold quantity, such as two milligrams, to illustrate its potency. The designation enables the use of weapon of mass destruction authorities and related policy measures to disrupt production, trafficking, and distribution, and to strengthen enforcement and regulatory actions by relevant agencies. The action explains the rationale for treating fentanyl as a WMD-level threat and directs coordination to implement applicable authorities and procedures. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/designating-fentanyl-as-a-weapon-of-mass-destruction/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Safeguard U.S. Investors from Foreign-Owned and Politically Motivated Proxy Advisory Firms]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order directs relevant federal departments and agencies to assess the influence of foreign-owned proxy advisory firms on U.S. corporate governance and investor decision-making. It notes that proxy advisory services—such as Institutional Shareholder Services Inc. and Glass, Lewis & Co., LLC—can affect shareholder voting policies and outcomes. The order requests actions to increase transparency of such services, evaluate risks associated with foreign ownership and politically motivated guidance, and implement safeguards to protect American investors and the integrity of capital markets. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/protecting-american-investors-from-foreign-owned-and-politically-motivated-proxy-advisors/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing a National Policy Framework for Artificial Intelligence and Eliminating State-Law Obstruction to National AI Policy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order states that United States leadership in artificial intelligence will promote national and economic security and maintain competitive advantage across multiple domains. It references Executive Order 14179 of January 23 and sets out the objective of establishing a national policy framework for artificial intelligence. The order addresses eliminating state-law obstructions to national AI policy and directs federal agencies to coordinate actions to develop, deploy, and govern artificial intelligence technologies in alignment with national interests. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/eliminating-state-law-obstruction-of-national-artificial-intelligence-policy/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation by the President designating National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates December 7, 2025, as National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day. The document recalls the attack on Pearl Harbor on December 7, 1941 and acknowledges the service and sacrifice of U.S. armed forces, civilian personnel, and others affected by the events. It calls for appropriate observances and reflection on the significance of Pearl Harbor, and it honors those who contributed to the nation's response and recovery during and after World War II. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/national-pearl-harbor-remembrance-day-2025-17fc/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aligning United States Core Childhood Vaccine Recommendations with Best Practices from Peer Developed Countries]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A memorandum issued to the Secretary of Health and Human Services and the Director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention directs agencies to review and align the United States' core childhood vaccination recommendations with established practices observed in peer developed countries. The document notes that, as of January 2025, the United States began recommending routine vaccination for all children against 18 diseases, including COVID-19, and tasks the involved agencies with evaluating international guidelines, safety and efficacy data, and implementation considerations to harmonize the U.S. immunization schedule with internationally recognized best practices. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>