<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Honoring the Memory of Specialist Sarah Beckstrom, West Virginia Army National Guard]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation, issued by the President, honors the memory of Specialist Sarah Beckstrom of the West Virginia Army National Guard. It asserts the President's constitutional and legal authority to act in observance and marks the memory by ordering a flag-related observance as part of the memorial. The document reflects an official act of remembrance for a service member. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/honoring-the-memory-of-specialist-sarah-beckstrom-west-virginia-army-national-guard/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/honoring-the-memory-of-specialist-sarah-beckstrom-west-virginia-army-national-guard/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Message on the Anniversary of the Monroe Doctrine (America 250)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This White House post presents a presidential message commemorating the anniversary of the Monroe Doctrine. It references the 1823 proclamation attributed to President James Monroe and describes the doctrine as a longstanding principle guiding United States sovereignty in the Western Hemisphere. The message states that the United States will defend the homeland, its interests, and the well-being of its citizens, and it notes that the current administration reaffirms these commitments on the anniversary of the doctrine. The post situates the doctrine within contemporary U.S. foreign policy and underscores ongoing emphasis on defending national security and sovereignty. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/america-250-presidential-message-on-the-anniversary-of-the-monroe-doctrine/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/america-250-presidential-message-on-the-anniversary-of-the-monroe-doctrine/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[America 250: Presidential Message Commemorating Mark Twain's 190th Birthday]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This White House post, part of the America 250 initiative, presents a presidential message commemorating Mark Twain on his 190th birthday. The message acknowledges Twain as a foundational American writer and summarizes his influence through humor, imagination, and storytelling, highlighting how his work reflects elements of the American spirit and his impact on American literature and culture. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/america-250-presidential-message-on-mark-twains-190th-birthday/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/america-250-presidential-message-on-mark-twains-190th-birthday/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Establishing the Genesis Mission to Promote Scientific Discovery and Technological Innovation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order establishes the Genesis Mission with the stated goal of promoting scientific discovery and technological innovation in the United States. It references the historical role of science and technology in driving national progress and describes a national objective to maintain and enhance the United States' position in global technology leadership. The document defines the purpose in Section 1, noting that federal priorities include coordinating research, development, and deployment efforts to accelerate progress and strengthen national competitiveness in technology across relevant sectors. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/launching-the-genesis-mission/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/launching-the-genesis-mission/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designation of Certain Muslim Brotherhood Chapters as Foreign Terrorist Organizations and Specially Designated Global Terrorists]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority of the Constitution and U.S. law including the Immigration and Nationality Act and the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, this presidential action designates specific Muslim Brotherhood chapters as Foreign Terrorist Organizations (FTOs) and as Specially Designated Global Terrorists (SDGTs). The designation enables the implementation and enforcement of sanctions and asset controls by relevant U.S. agencies, restricts financial transactions and support by U.S. persons, and directs agencies to regulate and enforce compliance with these designations. It includes definitions of terms used in the designation, outlines procedures for designation and potential delisting or modification, and assigns responsibilities to Federal departments and agencies for implementing sanctions and reporting. The action targets designated chapters and related entities to address national security concerns posed by these groups. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/designation-of-certain-muslim-brotherhood-chapters-as-foreign-terrorist-organizations-and-specially-designated-global-terrorists/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/designation-of-certain-muslim-brotherhood-chapters-as-foreign-terrorist-organizations-and-specially-designated-global-terrorists/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action Modifying the Scope of Tariffs on the Government of Brazil]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Under the authority vested in the President by the Constitution and U.S. law, including the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, the National Emergencies Act, and Section 604 of the Trade Act of 1974, this action modifies the scope of tariffs applicable to goods of the Government of Brazil. The action outlines revised tariff parameters affecting transactions involving the Government of Brazil and is published as an official presidential action. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/11/modifying-the-scope-of-tariffs-on-the-government-of-brazil/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>