<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations to the Senate for Michael Selig as Chairman and Commissioner of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission; withdrawal of Joel Rayburn's nomination]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House announced nominations for Michael Selig, of Florida, to serve as Chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (succeeding Rostin Behnam) and to serve as a Commissioner of the CFTC for a term expiring April 13, 2029 (succeeding Christy Goldsmith Romero). The announcement also indicated the withdrawal of Joel Rayburn's nomination to the Senate. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nominations-and-withdrawal-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation: Regulatory Relief for Certain Stationary Sources to Promote American Mineral Security]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The proclamation emphasizes copper's importance to the United States' energy, defense, and manufacturing sectors and highlights the role of domestic copper smelting capacity in reducing reliance on foreign supply chains. It describes regulatory relief for certain stationary sources as a measure intended to promote American mineral security and support domestic production capabilities. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-mineral-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nomination of Jennifer Wicks McNamara to be Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Jennifer Wicks McNamara, a resident of Virginia, has been nominated to serve as the United States Ambassador Extraordinary and Plenipotentiary to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. The nomination has been sent to the Senate for consideration, initiating the confirmation process. If confirmed, the nominee would serve as the chief U.S. diplomatic representative in Vietnam and oversee the U.S. Embassy’s activities, carrying out duties customary for the position and representing U.S. interests in the bilateral relationship, subject to Senate advice and consent. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/nomination-sent-to-the-senate/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Proclamation: National Day of Remembrance for Charlie Kirk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation designates a National Day of Remembrance in response to the assassination of Charlie Kirk on September 10, 2025, in a campus courtyard. The proclamation directs government bodies and the general public to observe the day and honor Charlie Kirk's memory, recognizing the impact of the event on the nation. The action is published as part of the White House's presidential actions for October 2025. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/10/national-day-of-remembrance-for-charlie-kirk/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>