<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:00:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Security Presidential Memorandum-7: Countering Domestic Terrorism and Organized Political Violence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential directive directing specified federal agencies to coordinate a comprehensive, whole-of-government strategy to counter domestic terrorism and organized political violence. The memorandum assigns responsibilities to relevant departments (State, Treasury, Justice, Homeland Security) to develop and implement policy actions, improve interagency information sharing and threat assessment, align resources, and pursue measures to disrupt, deter, and prevent such activities while complying with applicable laws. It emphasizes a coordinated approach across diplomatic, financial, law enforcement, and homeland security domains and seeks to establish priorities for actions and oversight. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/countering-domestic-terrorism-and-organized-political-violence/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/countering-domestic-terrorism-and-organized-political-violence/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Designating Antifa as a Domestic Terrorist Organization]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The document designates Antifa as a domestic terrorist organization, stating that the group advocates for the overthrow of the U.S. government and law enforcement, and employs illegal means to organize and pursue violent activities nationwide. The designation formalizes the classification and outlines its implications under applicable law. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/designating-antifa-as-a-domestic-terrorist-organization/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/designating-antifa-as-a-domestic-terrorist-organization/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Hispanic Heritage Month, 2025 Proclamation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation designates National Hispanic Heritage Month for 2025. It acknowledges the contributions of Hispanic-American citizens, past and present, and describes their ongoing commitment to shared American values. The proclamation highlights the resilience and spirit of the Hispanic-American community and notes that Hispanic-American patriots have served on the front lines of the U.S. military. The document serves to recognize the role of Hispanic-Americans in the nation’s history and society. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-hispanic-heritage-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-hispanic-heritage-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Constitution Week, 2025 Proclamation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential proclamation announcing Constitution Week 2025 to commemorate the 238th anniversary of the signing of the United States Constitution and to reaffirm the nation's commitment to the constitutional framework and civic responsibilities that sustain self-government. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/constitution-week-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/constitution-week-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>