<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum Directing Review and Withdrawal from International Organizations, Conventions, and Treaties Contrary to United States Interests]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This memorandum directs the heads of executive departments and agencies to implement Executive Order 14199, issued February 4, 2025, which authorizes the United States to withdraw from certain international organizations, conventions, and treaties deemed contrary to U.S. interests and to terminate funding associated with those entities. The memorandum describes the purpose, scope, and procedures for identifying target organizations, establishes timelines for withdrawal, outlines notification and coordination requirements, and requires reporting on actions taken. Agencies are instructed to assess existing obligations, safeguard national interests, and coordinate orderly disengagement, including winding down commitments, transferring responsibilities as needed, and communicating policy changes to relevant stakeholders. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/withdrawing-the-united-states-from-international-organizations-conventions-and-treaties-that-are-contrary-to-the-interests-of-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order: Prioritizing the Warfighter in Defense Contracting]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential executive order directs actions to prioritize defense contracting in support of the warfighter. Section 1 states the purpose as strengthening United States military warfighting capabilities and outlines the objective of aligning contracting processes and resources to enhance military readiness and the effectiveness of defense procurement. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/prioritizing-the-warfighter-in-defense-contracting/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nominations Sent to the Senate for U.S. Attorney in Maine and U.S. District Judge in Missouri, Among Other Nominations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The White House release titled Nominations Sent to the Senate lists nominations presented to the Senate, including Andrew Benson of Maine as United States Attorney for the District of Maine for a four-year term, succeeding Darcie N. McElwee, and Megan Blair Benton of Missouri as United States District Judge for the Western District of Missouri, succeeding M. Douglas Harpool. It also mentions a nomination from North Carolina named William Boyle for another United States position, though the specific post is not shown in the provided excerpt. The post is part of the January 2026 update to nominations published on The White House website. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2026/01/nominations-sent-to-the-senate-3f7b/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Concerning Amendments to Adjusting Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation describes the President's action under Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act to address national security concerns related to imports of timber, lumber, and their derivative products. It notes that on July 1, 2025, the Secretary of Commerce transmitted a report on the effects of these imports on national security as part of the Section 232 investigation. Based on that report, the proclamation provides for adjustments to the import regime for wood products to be implemented in order to address the identified national security risks, with applicable steps and timelines for enforcement. The action is documented in the White House's presidential actions release dated December 2025 and reflects the administration's use of executive authority to respond to the investigation's findings. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/amendments-to-adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Action to Implement the United States-Israel Agreement on Trade in Agricultural Products and Related Provisions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential action implements the United States-Israel Agreement on Trade in Agricultural Products, established within the United States-Israel Free Trade Area framework. It carries out provisions of the agreement and related measures authorized under the United States-Israel Free Trade Area Implementation Act, focusing on trade in agricultural products and other related purposes. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/to-implement-the-united-states-israel-agreement-on-trade-in-agricultural-products-and-for-other-purposes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/to-implement-the-united-states-israel-agreement-on-trade-in-agricultural-products-and-for-other-purposes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjustments of Certain Rates of Pay]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Issued under the President's constitutional and statutory authority, this Executive Order directs adjustments to the rates of basic pay for employees in statutory pay systems, as defined in 5 U.S.C. 5302(1). Section 1 establishes that these pay rates are to be set and adjusted under 5 U.S.C. 5303, thereby updating the basic pay rates for the statutory pay systems covered by the order. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/adjustments-of-certain-rates-of-pay/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Ensure American Space Superiority]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The executive order, issued by the President under the authority of the Constitution and federal law, establishes the policy and measures aimed at achieving space superiority for the United States. Section 1, titled Purpose, states that space superiority reflects national vision and resolve, and that the technologies developed to achieve space capability contribute substantially to the Nation's strength, security, and prosperity. The document outlines the rationale for pursuing space superiority and provides the foundation for related actions and agency responsibilities to implement the policy. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/ensuring-american-space-superiority/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Ordering Closure of Executive Departments and Agencies of the Federal Government on December 24, 2025, and December 26, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The order, issued under the President's constitutional and legal authority, requires all executive departments and agencies of the Federal Government to close and to excuse their employees from duty on Wednesday, December 24, 2025, and Friday, December 26, 2025. Section 1 establishes the directive for closure on the specified dates. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/providing-for-the-closure-of-executive-departments-and-agencies-of-the-federal-government-on-december-24-2025-and-december-26-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>