<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:00:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Adjusting Imports of Timber, Lumber, and Their Derivative Products into the United States]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation, issued by the President, references a report on a Section 232 investigation submitted by the Secretary of Commerce on July 1, 2025 regarding the effects of imports of timber, lumber, and their derivative products on United States national security. Based on the findings of this investigation, the President directs adjustments to the importation of timber, lumber, and their derivative products into the United States, and outlines the scope, legal authority (Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act of 1962), and implementation details for these adjustments as described in the proclamation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/adjusting-imports-of-timber-lumber-and-their-derivative-products-into-the-united-states/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order to Continue Certain Federal Advisory Committees]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This executive order, issued under the President's authority and consistent with the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. Appendix), directs the continuation through September 30, 2027 of the federal advisory committees listed in the document. It extends the charters and membership for these committees and maintains their responsibilities, reporting lines, and oversight under FACA. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/continuance-of-certain-federal-advisory-committees/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Presidential Memorandum Directing Enforcement of Federal Death Penalty Provisions in the District of Columbia for the Most Heinous Crimes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A presidential memorandum directed to the Attorney General and the United States Attorney for the District of Columbia directs the enforcement of federal death penalty statutes within the District of Columbia in cases involving the most serious crimes. The memorandum outlines the intended deterrent and punitive objectives, specifies the scope of enforcement for applicable prosecutions, and provides instructions for coordinating decision-making and procedures to apply capital punishment provisions in accordance with federal law and constitutional requirements. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/enforcing-the-death-penalty-laws-in-the-district-of-columbia-to-deter-and-punish-the-most-heinous-crimes/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Designating Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims and designates Gold Star Mother's and Family's Day for 2025 to recognize the sacrifices of Gold Star families whose loved ones died in service to the United States. The proclamation notes the nation’s obligation to honor and support these families and directs executive branch agencies to observe appropriate memorial observances. It also encourages the public to participate in activities that acknowledge and reflect upon the contributions and sacrifices of Gold Star families. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/gold-star-mothers-and-familys-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive Order Implementing the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act to Regulate Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications, Including TikTok]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The executive action references the Protecting Americans from Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (Public Law 118-50, Division H) and describes its authority to regulate foreign adversary controlled applications, with particular reference to applications operated by TikTok, and directs agencies to implement the Act's provisions to address national security considerations. The document outlines background and the legal basis for regulation under the Act. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/saving-tiktok-while-protecting-national-security/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Restricting Entry of Certain Nonimmigrant Workers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This presidential proclamation imposes restrictions on entry of certain nonimmigrant workers. It cites concerns that the H-1B visa program has been exploited to replace American workers with lower-paid, lower-skilled labor and describes the measures the administration will implement to limit entry for specified nonimmigrant categories. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/restriction-on-entry-of-certain-nonimmigrant-workers/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation on National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President proclaims National POW/MIA Recognition Day, 2025, to honor U.S. service members who were captured or reported missing in action and to acknowledge the experiences of their families. The proclamation states the nation's responsibility to account for missing personnel and to communicate the status of individuals held as prisoners of war. It designates observances and educational activities to commemorate the day and directs federal agencies to support appropriate ceremonies, public statements, and programs. It reiterates the commitment to locating, identifying, and repatriating missing service members where possible and to providing assistance to families, veterans, and survivors in connection with POW/MIA matters. The proclamation places these efforts in the broader context of military service and national remembrance, urging the country to reflect on the service and sacrifices of those affected by captivity and missing status. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/09/national-pow-mia-recognition-day-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>