<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Presidential Action Summaries]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:00:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation for National Foster Care Month, 2025]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation recognizes May 2025 as National Foster Care Month, highlighting the essential role families play in raising children and strengthening communities. It addresses the challenges faced by children and young people who find themselves without safe and loving care, and underscores the importance of supportive environments for their well-being. The proclamation calls attention to the need for ongoing efforts to provide stability and assistance to foster families and the children within the foster care system. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/05/national-foster-care-month-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/05/national-foster-care-month-2025/</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proclamation Recognizing the 80th Anniversary of Victory in Europe Day]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This proclamation commemorates the 80th anniversary of the Allied victory in Europe during World War II, marking the end of hostilities in Europe and acknowledging the significance of this event in the context of global history. The proclamation highlights the historic triumph over national socialism and fascism and serves to honor the contributions of those who served during the conflict. It reflects on the values of freedom and the importance of remembrance in the collective memory of the nation. Disclaimer: This content is AI generated. Use at your own risk. Please consult the original articles for accurate information.]]></description>
            <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/05/vcitory-day-for-world-war-ii-2025/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/05/vcitory-day-for-world-war-ii-2025/</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>