<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Presidential Action Summaries</title>
    <item>
      <title>Imposition of Tariffs on Canadian Goods to Combat Illicit Drug Trafficking</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/02/imposing-duties-to-address-the-flow-of-illicit-drugs-across-our-national-border/</link>
      <description>This Executive Order by the President responds to the influx of illicit drugs, particularly from Canada, by declaring a national emergency and imposing an additional 25% tariff on certain goods from Canada. It aims to enhance border security and public health by addressing the challenges posed by drug trafficking organizations. The measure involves cooperation with Canada and outlines specific enforcement actions to manage the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessment of Aviation Safety and Hiring Standards</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/immediate-assessment-of-aviation-safety/</link>
      <description>This memorandum instructs the Secretary of Transportation and the Administrator of the FAA to review recent hiring decisions and safety protocols to address concerns over aviation safety standards. It emphasizes a return to merit-based recruitment and aims to evaluate and correct any issues identified during the previous administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Order on Additional Measures to Combat Anti-Semitism</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/additional-measures-to-combat-anti-semitism/</link>
      <description>This Executive Order reaffirms previous actions to combat anti-Semitism in the United States, directing federal agencies to identify and utilize legal tools to address anti-Semitic harassment and violence, particularly in educational settings. It mandates reports from agencies to evaluate actions taken against anti-Semitism and ensures that civil rights are upheld for Jewish students. The order also encourages collaboration among various government departments to monitor and take necessary actions pertaining to anti-Semitic activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laken Riley Act: Custody of Charged Aliens</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/president-donald-j-trump-signed-s-5-into-law/</link>
      <description>The Laken Riley Act mandates that the Secretary of Homeland Security detain individuals charged with theft in the United States, among other provisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expansion of Migrant Operations Center at Naval Station Guantanamo Bay</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/expanding-migrant-operations-center-at-naval-station-guantanamo-bay-to-full-capacity/</link>
      <description>This memorandum directs the Secretary of Defense and the Secretary of Homeland Security to expand the Migrant Operations Center at Naval Station Guantanamo Bay to full capacity. The expansion aims to provide additional detention space for individuals identified as high-priority criminal aliens and to meet related immigration enforcement requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Order on Celebrating America's 250th Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/celebrating-americas-250th-birthday/</link>
      <description>This executive order establishes a task force to coordinate the celebration of the 250th anniversary of American Independence on July 4, 2026, including the creation of a National Garden of American Heroes and measures to protect monuments from vandalism. The task force will report on planning and activities leading up to the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Order on K-12 Education Policies and Parental Rights</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/ending-radical-indoctrination-in-k-12-schooling/</link>
      <description>This executive order aims to ensure compliance with federal laws prohibiting discrimination in K-12 education and to protect parental rights. It directs relevant agencies to develop a strategy to eliminate federal funding for certain educational practices perceived as discriminatory or ideological, while also reestablishing the 1776 Commission to promote patriotic education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing K-12 Educational Choice and Opportunities for Families</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/expanding-educational-freedom-and-opportunity-for-families/</link>
      <description>This executive order aims to support parental choice in the education of their children by directing federal resources towards K-12 educational alternatives. It mandates guidance and reviews from various federal agencies to explore funding options and improve education access, particularly for low-income families and military families. The initiative seeks to foster competition among educational institutions to enhance overall student achievement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Order on Medical Procedures Involving Minors</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/protecting-children-from-chemical-and-surgical-mutilation/</link>
      <description>This executive order outlines the U.S. government's position on medical procedures for minors related to gender transition, prohibiting federal funding or support for these procedures and instructing health agencies to review existing practices and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinstatement of Service Members Discharged for Refusing COVID-19 Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/reinstating-service-members-discharged-under-the-militarys-covid-19-vaccination-mandate/</link>
      <description>This executive order allows service members who were discharged for refusing the COVID-19 vaccine to request reinstatement, revert to their former rank, and receive back pay and benefits. It also enables individuals who voluntarily left the service due to the mandate to return without penalty. The Secretary of Defense and Secretary of Homeland Security must report on the implementation of this order within 60 days.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

